<pairs>
	<pair hash="4242E614B12C72055FE3ABEA568BD307D4092AC8DA3CA0A52B2A331240FF6491">
		<old>Contact an authorized Kia dealer for more details.</old>
		<new>Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
		<new>Consult an authorized Kia dealer for more details.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="868DD52C897DFE347F14EFE98ECC8C5BE19EFD5B676E1E424CF55B8C21449D3F">
		<old>If you are unsure how to use or replace the battery, contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If you are unsure how to use or replace the battery, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="545BE56A997AE12B430FBEE616C81944E8510FD8F00CB79A728C559DA820AFD3">
		<old>Do not modify or repair any part of the power liftgate by yourself. This must be done by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Do not modify or repair any part of the power liftgate by yourself. This must be done by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="F25FE1DA54403C8009241C3754099D0DD1EE9629C667EC853EA058CA2A49E2DA">
		<old>If the fuel filler door does not open under certain conditions, such as an electrical malfunction, contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the fuel filler door does not open under certain conditions, such as an electrical malfunction, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="8684C69DE18B0E9912B372B713F1F49C83C5EBB1126FE98BC9BB94D9139C6662">
		<old>Even small amounts of the wrong fuel could result in damage to the fuel system and the engine. Have the system serviced by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Even small amounts of the wrong fuel could result in damage to the fuel system and the engine. Have the system serviced by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="95F0382A7C4966C94530E3D85BD48613F2DC39E782AD42B6880C9AFCE254757A">
		<old>Have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="0335C2D33B3B33C80E60292902C59C4369855646D09597AAC55B838F7AEB9C63">
		<old>Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer as soon as possible.</old>
		<new>Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="A7E4880E8FB47524C9D8819343751DFEEEDB24994870DB40CB27CE4FECCC0F0D">
		<old>If the warning light remains on after the sensor has been uncovered or unblocked when Forward/Side Safety is on, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the warning light remains on after the sensor has been uncovered or unblocked when Forward/Side Safety is on, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1405E25DBF3A3B16A3A0C14B8B111A3BDA38882881392F966CCC04A7598904DA">
		<old>If the SRS airbag warning light remains illuminated while the vehicle is being driven, have the vehicle checked and repaired by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the SRS airbag warning light remains illuminated while the vehicle is being driven, have your vehicle inspected and repaired by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="2E32AF248A8C289F40C2E6533EED2C1A590049E6753C66EDD30F605F946C1C0F">
		<old>Air bags can only be used once– have an authorized Kia dealer replace the air bag immediately after deployment.</old>
		<new>Air bags can only be used once– have the system replaced by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="A0DA95EA2D1B93857438C32041D72DE00761DD8ED2DAC71B4C819E6E600FC331">
		<old>If your vehicle was flooded and has soaked carpeting or water on flooring, you shouldn't try to start the vehicle; In this situation, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. For cleaning the airbag pad covers, use only a soft, dry cloth or one which has been moistened with plain water. Solvents or cleaners could adversely affect the airbag covers and proper deployment of the system.</old>
		<new>If your vehicle was flooded and has soaked carpeting or water on flooring, you shouldn't try to start the vehicle; In this situation, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. For cleaning the airbag pad covers, use only a soft, dry cloth or one which has been moistened with plain water. Solvents or cleaners could adversely affect the airbag covers and proper deployment of the system.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="5432B087E80F77027A0AF29AC12F29E95FF11E2316C739539974332B76389F3E">
		<old>If the installation location or angle of the sensors is altered in any way, the airbags may deploy when they should not or they may not deploy when they should, causing severe injury or death. Therefore, do not try to perform maintenance on or around the airbag sensors. Have the vehicle checked and repaired by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the installation location or angle of the sensors is altered in any way, the airbags may deploy when they should not or they may not deploy when they should, causing severe injury or death. Therefore, do not try to perform maintenance on or around the airbag sensors. Have your vehicle inspected and repaired by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1EE009063F2FDA322A3CF1FF4E533A5E6E4B8FFDBC22CE87A92C8FF420EDF634">
		<old>Do not tamper with or disconnect wiring or other components of the SRS system, including the addition of any kind of badges to the pad covers or modifications to the body structure. Doing so could adversely affect SRS performance and lead to possible injury. If necessary, have the system serviced by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Do not tamper with or disconnect wiring or other components of the SRS system, including the addition of any kind of badges to the pad covers or modifications to the body structure. Doing so could adversely affect SRS performance and lead to possible injury. If necessary, have the system serviced by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="DE1114D74FC6FC3B83F30B981A2E56116837614750264F956E862DC116BAC64E">
		<old>SRS and pre-tensioners contain explosive chemicals. If you scrape a vehicle without removing the SRS and pre-tensioners, it may cause a fire. Before scraping a vehicle, contact an authorized Kia dealer</old>
		<new>SRS and pre-tensioners contain explosive chemicals. If you scrape a vehicle without removing the SRS and pre-tensioners, it may cause a fire. Before scraping a vehicle, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
		<new>SRS and pre-tensioners contain explosive chemicals. If you scrape a vehicle without removing the SRS and pre-tensioners, it may cause a fire. Before scraping a vehicle, consult an authorized Kia dealer</new>
		<new>SRS and pre-tensioners contain explosive chemicals. If you scrape a vehicle without removing the SRS and pre-tensioners, it may cause a fire. Before scraping a vehicle, contact an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="11BB92768AB02C7B62746F912D6C28A13308B5A633625AB444B43643018779B2">
		<old>Never try to open or repair any components of the curtain airbag system. If necessary, have the system serviced by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Never try to open or repair any components of the curtain airbag system. If necessary, have the system serviced by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="38EA6EBC383BDC7681C556BF63851298329F5097063A1D08827C47916E57A727">
		<old>Problems may arise if you change the sensor installation angles due to deformation of the front bumper, body, or B pillar where the side collision sensors are installed. In this case, have the system serviced by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Problems may arise if you change the sensor installation angles due to deformation of the front bumper, body, or B pillar where the side collision sensors are installed. In this case, have the system serviced by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="783DED1E3C0AC36867A76A382478426EB6EE77828AC1A20D29CEC3EE5C3B6D4F">
		<old>If any of the following conditions occur, this indicates a malfunction in the air bag system. Have an authorized Kia dealer inspect the air bag system as soon as possible.</old>
		<new>If any of the following conditions occur, this indicates a malfunction in the air bag system. Have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
		<new>If any of the following conditions occur, this indicates a malfunction in the air bag system. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="CA29FEB83CFD674BF905B67399AB9F88EF8F93F4CF0AF6F01E343E483AF9BA45">
		<old>When Ground View Monitor is not working properly, the screen flickers, or the camera image does not display normally, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the Ground View Monitor does not work properly, the screen flickers, or the camera image does not display properly, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="7E2D7162D6FA52D31CE6E9610C98DD2E9378FAE24C00B66E4BCF14B5EA4EB8B0">
		<old>If this occurs, have the function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer as soon as possible.</old>
		<new>If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E8DAAF600C391A73AFCEBFDF3420511860E5E49E081D6358B4935348ABAC8518">
		<old>If there is no alert until the maximum maintenance interval, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If there is no alert until the maximum maintenance interval, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="0B2EC6190CD70674B76A947AA4E610628A355C865A76290CCFB78896E9F2E30B">
		<old>If the fluid level is excessively low, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the fluid level is excessively low, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="77D11931F4966BC807F4C186363FA614DEB2DA0BC2CC667096874F8B80A09689">
		<old>If the LED lamp is not functioning, please have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. The LED lamp cannot be replaced as an individual component since it is an integrated unit. Instead, the entire LED lamp unit must be replaced.</old>
		<new>If the LED lamp is not functioning, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. The LED lamp cannot be replaced as an individual component since it is an integrated unit. Instead, the entire LED lamp unit must be replaced.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1937907DFE5803CF65CA2FB2A70A9F99AA46837A55259B544D9A7AE044ECED32">
		<old>If you use the wheels on the market, use a TPMS sensor approved by an authorized Kia dealer/service partner.</old>
		<new>If you use the wheels on the market, use a TPMS sensor approved by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D685BD567E215E66EB4BD4C7952DA26281AE28EA8406F19868926356550DFBAE">
		<old>Winter puts additional burdens on the battery system. Visually inspect the battery and cables as described in section 8. Have your battery inspected by an authorized Kia dealer to verify the charge level.</old>
		<new>Winter puts additional burdens on the battery system. Visually inspect the battery and cables as described in section 8. Have your battery inspected by an authorized Kia dealer to verify the charge level.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="806CEA8BC3EF91FD44057CF4E42C1FDCBDE6B9FAC606CE14813700769B3F6211">
		<old>In some climates it is recommended that a lower “winter weight” oil be used during cold weather. See <xref/>. If you aren't sure what weight oil you should use, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>In some climates it is recommended that a lower “winter weight” oil be used during cold weather. See <xref/>. If you aren't sure what weight oil you should use, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="2AE19AEE4D2958C9B07C95619D861C14EBEC4508E52083F8931A4EACBD0B9D3F">
		<old>Never add any fuel system cleaning agents to the fuel tank other than what has been specified. (Consult an authorized Kia dealer for details.)</old>
		<new>Never add any fuel system cleaning agents to the fuel tank other than what has been specified. (Consult an authorized Kia dealer for details.)</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D9BBFD4062B074BE917985E1F47B17A6BBE1C0C59580F95A3D6616F3B825474D">
		<old>Contact an authorized Kia dealer</old>
		<new>Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="A1ED564D681A8EB151A6C5A9A65F84AA6D65115DCC49BF269E695EA36914C1E7">
		<old>For smart key replacement, visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>For smart key replacement, visit an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="BABB5E9932582DABDEF8FB2CE01A7CF88915A02BB45C2B10A1582B6A3EBD6567">
		<old>The smart key is designed to give you years of trouble-free use, however it can malfunction if exposed to moisture or static electricity. If you are unsure how to use or replace the battery, contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The smart key is designed to give you years of trouble-free use, however it can malfunction if exposed to moisture or static electricity. If you are unsure how to use or replace the battery, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3A8129679D9BF09E7550F7CEE5D3E2333C6F5BCA59EF4381302A9076F2D0DDE2">
		<old>When the smart key does not work correctly, open and close the door with the mechanical key and if you want to purchase them, contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the smart key does not work correctly, open and close the door with the mechanical key and if you want to purchase them, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="46DF042A4CA0424C7AAFD006E47E3FCFD78F53074F451C1B0EE15EB9846CAAF0">
		<old>If you need additional keys or lose your keys, contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If you need additional keys or lose your keys, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="A66974CD35EAD8D7AF3D871E9CA35A8FBAEB11AA4CC62787300C03D825C65570">
		<old>If you want this feature, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If you want this feature, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="C76B3132F2B77671554633DB2E475A145180B9294FF02D571C32F0E4B3EFAECA">
		<old>Should you notice any change in the effort required to steer during normal vehicle operation, have the power steering inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Should you notice any change in the effort required to steer during normal vehicle operation, have the power steering inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="982A037D7F1191F0C14278CD694280BAB697D6926A2A69E08E3AFF696FE3632F">
		<old>If the Motor Driven Power Steering system does not operate normally, the warning light will appear on the instrument cluster. The steering wheel may become difficult to control or operate abnormally. In this case, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the Motor Driven Power Steering system does not operate normally, the warning light will appear on the instrument cluster. The steering wheel may become difficult to control or operate abnormally. In this case, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="CC74C77FC0D019CE9866C560AD45504E597849358CCE4D1C26176DDA0F2E0417">
		<old>If the integrated memory system does not operate normally, have the system checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the integrated memory system does not operate normally, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="883F90AC649752BDBE9B95DC0CA7EFCE65D005369BB637079517D9FAC638DB3C">
		<old>However, if the Service Indicator (<image/>) and Malfunction Indicator Lamp (MIL) (<image/>) turn on when the SOC gauge is near the “L (Low)” or “0” level, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer as soon as possible.</old>
		<new>However, if the Service Indicator (<image/>) and Malfunction Indicator Lamp (MIL) (<image/>) turn on when the SOC gauge is near the “L (Low)” or “0” level, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer as soon as possible.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="2B6CC2F070FA17071B39B4F46EC7F2B9D5482EFAC270ED43F027011183A26966">
		<old>This message is displayed when charging is stopped because the charging connector is not correctly connected to the charging inlet. If this occurs, separate the charging connector, re-connect it and check whether there is any problem (external damage, foreign substances, etc.) with the charging connector and charging inlet. If the problem recurs even after replacing charging cable or genuine Kia portable charger, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>This message is displayed when charging is stopped because the charging connector is not correctly connected to the charging inlet. If this occurs, separate the charging connector, re-connect it and check whether there is any problem (external damage, foreign substances, etc.) with the charging connector and charging inlet. If the problem recurs even after replacing charging cable or genuine Kia portable charger, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="55153A4C38E453B0C3AD71E3E92088A6D0A35672EE3AB5A58C75D45F0B1A838C">
		<old>When there is a malfunction with the SRS. Have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When there is a malfunction with the SRS. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="9605C0F740B7DB9DDBB10D98F179C25B28A9DE05BE0BF32E42CE85A0F3A655EB">
		<old>If the light remains on, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the light remains on, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="2F1CC96A45E074517D25551CB70DBA2A3B78F80B2F4610D54CDDCB19DA1B9C65">
		<old>When the ABS and regular brake system are not working, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the ABS and regular brake system are not working, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="DD5E9521DDED47C5C7728CB9AF1555203B428954BD31048BC0BA150B15EFFFAC">
		<old>If the MIL appears, potential catalytic converter damage is possible which could result in loss of engine power. Have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the MIL appears, potential catalytic converter damage is possible which could result in loss of engine power. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E050865942690F9015BDB9AA6AC71546EB7EA5DBDC8D1022E324D37A52AE1E3A">
		<old>If the warning light remains on after adding oil or if oil is not available, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. Continuing driving with the warning light on may cause engine failure.</old>
		<new>If the warning light remains on after adding oil or if oil is not available, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. Continuing driving with the warning light on may cause engine failure.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D14A1EE6F1E1A7CCB18D5AAE99275C2254F624CEE1764AA3619453B833FD326E">
		<old>If this warning light blinks after following this procedure, have the GPF system checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If this warning light blinks after following this procedure, have the GPF system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="12F66E27D424EE2AF558F7A388CE445C6DCE6C21CC762221F4F3DE118AF06D26">
		<old>Yellow: When there is a malfunction with the auto hold system. Have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Yellow: When there is a malfunction with the auto hold system. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E2C416A7C1467E8DE933DB8144F3680CB028E2C0330202B7783FBD5BDC5E4FD8">
		<old>If any of the following occurs, there may be a malfunction with the turn signal system. Have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If any of the following occurs, there may be a malfunction with the turn signal system. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="7759379525786F663B4A9AF8E0211BDCDE6F5B6FAA508CE39F9C0D19CE5B5E5B">
		<old>When HBA is not working properly, the Check High Beam Assist (HBA) system warning message will appear and warning light (<image/>) will appear on the cluster. Have the function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When HBA is not working properly, the Check High Beam Assist (HBA) system warning message will appear and warning light (<image/>) will appear on the cluster. Have the function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="23EA041190615DF7D0A9C29F59416637AF9A3FC7DEB71EEACCBA142372E70416">
		<old>If the pre-tensioner seat belt system is not working properly, this warning light will appear even if there is not a malfunction with the SRS air bag. If the SRS air bag warning light does not illuminate when the <term>ENGINE START/STOP</term> button is turned to <term>ON</term>, or if it remains illuminated after appearing for approximately 6 seconds, or if it appears while the vehicle is being driven, have an authorized Kia dealer inspect the pre-tensioner seat belt and SRS air bag system as soon as possible.</old>
		<new>If the pre-tensioner seat belt system is not working properly, this warning light will appear even if there is not a malfunction with the SRS air bag. If the SRS air bag warning light does not illuminate when the <term>ENGINE START/STOP</term> button is turned to <term>ON</term>, or if it remains illuminated after appearing for approximately 6 seconds, or if it appears while the vehicle is being driven, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="BBDA238F7E3DA93D27965F9852ED6ABCD567BF0C79D98F1B1669D86806A82F1E">
		<old>Pre-tensioners are designed to operate only one time. After activation, pre-tensioner seat belts must be replaced. If the pre-tensioner must be replaced, contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Pre-tensioners are designed to operate only one time. After activation, pre-tensioner seat belts must be replaced. If the pre-tensioner must be replaced, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="5A43946458871105A09073D13536EAC1143143656E5ADBBC664B3BF94326F32F">
		<old>Always have the LATCH system inspected by your authorized Kia dealer after an accident. An accident can damage the LATCH system and may not properly secure the child restraint.</old>
		<new>Always have the LATCH system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer after an accident. An accident can damage the LATCH system and may not properly secure the child restraint.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="07C96FBA8B4A321CCCF7A0493477D7231D25B1EDA570DC5480BBBB3FCE05BE6B">
		<old>If the air bag warning light appears for more than 6 seconds after the <term>ENGINE START/STOP</term> button has been turned to the <term>ON</term> position, or if it appears during vehicle operation, an SRS component may not be functioning properly and you should have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the air bag warning light appears for more than 6 seconds after the <term>ENGINE START/STOP</term> button has been turned to the <term>ON</term> position, or if it appears during vehicle operation, an SRS component may not be functioning properly and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B8BD322EE8AC3B04724D9430F0F62EF8725B6EE41F50A5480A16ED190D98F13B">
		<old>If this occurs, have your vehicle immediately inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="66C07541125ADE38EE2867D82810705E6186AA17B9C0BB3D00F87ED85A67277A">
		<old>However, if the Service Indicator (<image/>) and Malfunction Indicator Lamp (MIL) (<image/>) turn on when the SOC gauge is near the “L (Low)” level, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>However, if the Service Indicator (<image/>) and Malfunction Indicator Lamp (MIL) (<image/>) turn on when the SOC gauge is near the “L (Low)” level, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="61AC4F275089B825425EE9474EE14BDC3359FDE3FF8957711B67E3279347037C">
		<old>When the ready indicator goes <term>OFF</term> or blinks, there is a problem with the system. If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the ready indicator goes <term>OFF</term> or blinks, there is a problem with the system. If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="A986FED782C94D160E41375645AF312F2D023B18DB9F36CBD790F22E8A0E7389">
		<old>This message is displayed when charging is stopped because the charging connector is not correctly connected to the charging inlet. If this occurs, separate the charging connector and re-connect it and check whether there is any problem (external damage, foreign substances, etc.) with the charging connector and charging inlet. If the same problem occurs when charging the vehicle with a replaced charging cable or genuine Kia portable charger, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>This message is displayed when charging is stopped because the charging connector is not correctly connected to the charging inlet. If this occurs, separate the charging connector and re-connect it and check whether there is any problem (external damage, foreign substances, etc.) with the charging connector and charging inlet. If the same problem occurs when charging the vehicle with a replaced charging cable or genuine Kia portable charger, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="8D927CBB54BA290B62037FB9AF44F868D7C3DAAE985B917591E1AD7AA3FE6CA7">
		<old>Your vehicle is equipped with orange colored insulation and covers over the high voltage components to protect people from electric shock. High voltage warning labels are attached to some system components as additional warnings. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Your vehicle is equipped with orange colored insulation and covers over the high voltage components to protect people from electric shock. High voltage warning labels are attached to some system components as additional warnings. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="56FC482840FD428848703E910FEACD08E190E3CD27A33C682D265BB26243DEA8">
		<old>The service interlock connector, located within the motor compartment, is a safety device that disables the high voltage of the battery. It’s for vehicle inspections by your authorized Kia dealer. Have your vehicle by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The service interlock connector, located within the motor compartment, is a safety device that disables the high voltage of the battery. It’s for vehicle inspections by an authorized Kia dealer. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="2FA5C395ECA4F517EDB364CEBEAC4F8253F90EE570E001385396D51DEDE45645">
		<old>Immediately call an emergency services or contact an authorized Kia dealer and advise them that a hybrid vehicle is involved.</old>
		<new>Immediately call an emergency services or consult an authorized Kia dealer and advise them that a hybrid vehicle is involved.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E17F0F3B437472D4AE089100DC7EF4C9AD272EBB8B0073BEEE6DF63CCA8D53C6">
		<old>Upon witnessing any sparks, gases, flames, or fuel leakage of your vehicle, immediately call emergency services or contact an authorized Kia dealer. Also, advise them that a hybrid vehicle is involved.</old>
		<new>Upon witnessing any sparks, gases, flames, or fuel leakage of your vehicle, immediately call emergency services or consult an authorized Kia dealer. Also, advise them that a hybrid vehicle is involved.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3AD67DBAADAFF5B73F32FAFEA7BC273044152094838002EC1840838B6FB0D84A">
		<old>Immediately contact an authorized Kia dealer and advise them that a hybrid vehicle is involved.</old>
		<new>Immediately consult an authorized Kia dealer and advise them that a hybrid vehicle is involved.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="42E3B06B608CCB72EF078C95F3014A0C9EED3C58B25FE0512A3D936A108EDA7A">
		<old>If the update or recovery fails, contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the update or recovery fails, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="394418297F3BA1E413C36CE82FDA0A5FD972B40A63463E0518FF013F8FDFDBA0">
		<old>If the airflow from the air vents suddenly decreases, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the airflow from the air vents suddenly decreases, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="A7167633858120E0D93052BFC3D37215F37AB84984C9D3236BE5F1FECB1752DA">
		<old>If abnormal operation occurs, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If abnormal operation occurs, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
		<new>If abnormal operation occurs, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="C9C3B7347592B0CE155A4A567F2A1BA02A187F5B2CDBD0345795F75D4E6F9BE0">
		<old>To purchase luggage nets, contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>To purchase luggage nets, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="FE511E7B5F8CDCB7C8BB6D5A4ED8B9AE56E6799C0A54878C8224888533E5A09E">
		<old>If you hear a change in the sound of the exhaust or if you drive over something that strikes the under side of the vehicle, have the exhaust system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If you hear a change in the sound of the exhaust or if you drive over something that strikes the under side of the vehicle, have the exhaust system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1AB4CA64068783DFCCB8045577E0311020CFA1766412E94D12D58ECC8F387F13">
		<old>Immediately have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer</old>
		<new>Immediately have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1C8A8CAC5066B7EA4A93B0E1DA96861296128D1B63F6147AE1EB913A04BFCD96">
		<old>Jump start your vehicle (refer to <xref/>) or contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Jump start your vehicle (refer to <xref/>) or consult an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="934998891842E7299D6EE992E13DCE1DA2407F9340C356788488990747943EA8">
		<old>Be careful not to apply unnecessary force on the radar sensor or sensor cover. If the sensor is forcibly moved out of proper alignment, the Smart Regeneration System may not operate correctly. In this case, a warning message may not be displayed. Have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Be careful not to apply unnecessary force on the radar sensor or sensor cover. If the sensor is forcibly moved out of proper alignment, the Smart Regeneration System may not operate correctly. In this case, a warning message may not be displayed. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="4C026C2FBFCD4500841BC306EF72FA303EE6F37A6AB2D33D88CBEE4F266E9ED9">
		<old>If the front bumper becomes damaged in the area around the radar sensor, the Smart Regeneration System may not operate properly. Have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the front bumper becomes damaged in the area around the radar sensor, the Smart Regeneration System may not operate properly. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="21A791F451837065A78AA1FF93AA4C3F4D3690A63F747193255B0D4840416988">
		<old>The message will appear when the system is not functioning normally. The system will be canceled and the word 'AUTO' on the cluster will disappear and instead display regenerative braking level. Check for foreign substances on the front radar. Remove any dirt, snow, or foreign material that could interfere with the radar sensors. If the system still does not operate normally, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The message will appear when the system is not functioning normally. The system will be canceled and the word 'AUTO' on the cluster will disappear and instead display regenerative braking level. Check for foreign substances on the front radar. Remove any dirt, snow, or foreign material that could interfere with the radar sensors. If the system still does not operate normally, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="08739BF5E67F44338B4E2C0B2FCD3F112A02C9E116AA71A64CE1FD3A1B7A1F88">
		<old>If the AWD warning light (<image/>) stays on the instrument cluster, your vehicle may have a malfunction with the AWD system. When the AWD warning light (<image/>) appears, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the AWD warning light (<image/>) stays on the instrument cluster, your vehicle may have a malfunction with the AWD system. When the AWD warning light (<image/>) appears, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="4A55EE70C71BA20162C8C400BAF681C7D2A63A99C58D21FC0DEF8B2A5DED4AC8">
		<old>If the warning messages in the LCD display continue to blink, for your safety, have the system checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the warning messages in the LCD display continue to blink, for your safety, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="384907981D80A749A163DBE5905467E881E89C734CB1ACAC732BE06E75B7E4C0">
		<old>If you notice a continuous noise or burning smell when the <term>EPB</term> is used for emergency braking, Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If you notice a continuous noise or burning smell when the <term>EPB</term> is used for emergency braking, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="63C9E9FAE91551A04E18FBDD4BA60480880719B0621F8E723F61C20E6BCE033F">
		<old>If the parking brake warning light remains on even though the <term>EPB</term> has been released, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the parking brake warning light remains on even though the <term>EPB</term> has been released, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="42F346A99B8EA786F84398C83A543A64915A39C3D4B3A0E6D91DB16CB2D308CD">
		<old>The <term>EPB</term> warning light may appear if the <term>EPB</term> switch operates abnormally. Shut off and turn it on again after a few minutes. The warning light should go off and the <term>EPB</term> switch will operate normally. If the <term>EPB</term> warning light is still on, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The <term>EPB</term> warning light may appear if the <term>EPB</term> switch operates abnormally. Shut off and turn it on again after a few minutes. The warning light should go off and the <term>EPB</term> switch will operate normally. If the <term>EPB</term> warning light is still on, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="6467A3015282706F92AF4B8451CC842A42DEA916F5F6BB13E063823B54D596FE">
		<old>If the parking brake warning light blinks when the <term>EPB</term> warning light is on, press the <term>EPB</term> switch, then pull it up. Press it back to its original position and pull it back up. If the <term>EPB</term> warning does not turn off, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the parking brake warning light blinks when the <term>EPB</term> warning light is on, press the <term>EPB</term> switch, then pull it up. Press it back to its original position and pull it back up. If the <term>EPB</term> warning does not turn off, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="C591873C03F5565708A3EE6F460D52D0BC5F11995C38345CE041B53FF0D34459">
		<old>If the <term>EPB</term> does not release normally, load your vehicle onto a flatbed tow truck and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the <term>EPB</term> does not release normally, load your vehicle onto a flatbed tow truck and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="9ED6839C4575C5964789B554B113DA81F5FE2DE453254E84257A92D6F8465D73">
		<old>If the <term>AUTO HOLD</term> indicator lights up yellow, the Auto Hold is not working properly. Have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the <term>AUTO HOLD</term> indicator lights up yellow, the Auto Hold is not working properly. Have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="8FE3E42B81F9FA405F10E31B2B35918CA754C7352D041DE0CFD6AE39987756D5">
		<old>Have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="7915F6C8C6B543D6D4E461D786C50FBA89FFF55C50C94C3A02F8321BEEB27FDC">
		<old>The ABS will perform self-diagnosis and the light will go off if everything is normal. If the light stays on, you may have a problem with your ABS. Visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The ABS will perform self-diagnosis and the light will go off if everything is normal. If the light stays on, you may have a problem with your ABS. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="7559B94F994C37A7C366D09E8C933CA8F9B6135370B0DDF4E97F7A9AFC56F8C6">
		<old>Restart the vehicle. If the ABS warning light goes off, your ABS is normal. Otherwise, you may have a problem with the ABS. Visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Restart the vehicle. If the ABS warning light goes off, your ABS is normal. Otherwise, you may have a problem with the ABS. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3EE14BD7718019601945527510B34A01C5E91C7315F5A516B5A24B6A795C63D0">
		<old>If the DBC yellow indicator light appears, the system may have overheated or malfunctioned. When the warning light appears even though the DBC system has cooled off, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the DBC yellow indicator light appears, the system may have overheated or malfunctioned. When the warning light appears even though the DBC system has cooled off, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="DCE367947C1A5878421C079AB520C5FAD94FDAC66E6DECD21F764597CB287F27">
		<old>If the ESC (<image/>) or MDPS (<image/>) warning light stays illuminated or blinks, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the ESC (<image/>) or MDPS (<image/>) warning light stays illuminated or blinks, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="51217DDF490ED48EAB32AE750A7EEF099B9F76EA04F0BCC908BAC01313BDA41F">
		<old>The VSM can be deactivated even if you don't cancel the VSM operation by pressing the <term>ESC OFF</term> button. It indicates that a malfunction has been detected in the EPS or VSM system. If the ESC indicator light (<image/>) or EPS warning light remains on, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The VSM can be deactivated even if you don't cancel the VSM operation by pressing the <term>ESC OFF</term> button. It indicates that a malfunction has been detected in the EPS or VSM system. If the ESC indicator light (<image/>) or EPS warning light remains on, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="4C11A22EC165D388A74509110A302F507C698589BB18107F4B2FE9AB6C322F8B">
		<old>To dry the brakes, apply the brakes lightly until the braking action returns to normal, taking care to always keep the vehicle under control. If the braking action does not return to normal, stop as soon as it is safe to do so and visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>To dry the brakes, apply the brakes lightly until the braking action returns to normal, taking care to always keep the vehicle under control. If the braking action does not return to normal, stop as soon as it is safe to do so and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D032CD3CFFD8C6E90B1AD82C65D9B63D51529739EA0A18C277DE705511B80741">
		<old>The SRS functions only when the vehicle is in the ON position and remains functional for approximately 3 minutes after the vehicle is turned OFF. If the SRS airbag warning light does not appear or stays on for more than approximately 6 seconds when the vehicle is in the ON position, or if it turns on while driving after the vehicle is started, the SRS is malfunctioning. In this case, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The SRS functions only when the vehicle is in the ON position and remains functional for approximately 3 minutes after the vehicle is turned OFF. If the SRS airbag warning light does not appear or stays on for more than approximately 6 seconds when the vehicle is in the ON position, or if it turns on while driving after the vehicle is started, the SRS is malfunctioning. In this case, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="A277188C86FD40AC862CC0263038107FEF1359E806C8E757AEE3B565FB186074">
		<old>Any service related to the passenger seat and the ODS must be done at an authorized Kia dealership.</old>
		<new>Any service related to the passenger seat and the ODS must be done at an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D4B00E441B360DA2358F02D2ED131652E6DE7BBE2020E39D80070EBAB55965E8">
		<old>Laws vary for towing trailers, cars, or other types of vehicles or apparatus may differ by state. Consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Laws vary for towing trailers, cars, or other types of vehicles or apparatus may differ by state. Consult an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="CC545CC13BD888493136FAC8B31DB2D1698587BB09616AE856C52FAA34BD3BB4">
		<old>When towing a trailer, consult an authorized Kia dealer for additional requirements such as a towing kit, etc.</old>
		<new>When towing a trailer, consult an authorized Kia dealer for additional requirements such as a towing kit, etc.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E6D8148D538E56F5EEA71D707F873ADDA64AB5B8BB5669F24590736A044B59CD">
		<old>If the detection sensors have been replaced or repaired, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the detection sensors have been replaced or repaired, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="31E2CD46F6EE1084EA9FA6A8B6649BBE2405C241F232F7158EEF5CA564B04BE2">
		<old>If the radar or around the radar experiences an impact, Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist may not operate properly even if a warning message is not displayed on the cluster. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the radar or around the radar experiences an impact, Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist may not operate properly even if a warning message is not displayed on the cluster. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="8205BD93E9691A532622677EA557BF799323A44D749E73387D49E780B064CC1E">
		<old>The driver can monitor Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist On/Off status from the Settings menu. If the Forward Safety warning light (<image/>) or Emergency steering warning light (<image/>) remains <term>ON</term> when Forward safety or Forward/side safety is selected, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The driver can monitor Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist On/Off status from the Settings menu. If the Forward Safety warning light (<image/>) or Emergency steering warning light (<image/>) remains <term>ON</term> when Forward safety or Forward/side safety is selected, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="4D0428FAEDAFF6CF22CE55CEF0279C1437FDD1F7BDEF2E1B1BEDAD0D464F7BC6">
		<old>When Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist is not working properly, a warning message will appear, and the Forward Safety warning light (<image/>), the Emergency steering warning light (<image/>) and the Master warning light (<image/>) will appear on the cluster. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist is not working properly, a warning message will appear, and the Forward Safety warning light (<image/>), the Emergency steering warning light (<image/>) and the Master warning light (<image/>) will appear on the cluster. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="2265AD6AA7B85AF329F86D8491C9CF63614CAEFDC7D86170BA75AA53BFDC0709">
		<old>If Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist does not operate properly after obstruction (snow, rain, or foreign material) is removed (including trailer, carrier, etc. from the rear bumper), have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer as soon as possible.</old>
		<new>If Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist does not operate properly after obstruction (snow, rain, or foreign material) is removed (including trailer, carrier, etc. from the rear bumper), have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="284063D509B4F8C3FEB4FD7DC856960DCE6C24E110170D1267EA38922A5E0568">
		<old>If Lane Keeping Assist still does not operate normally after cleaning foreign materials (snow, rain, etc.) or removing obstructions (including trailer, carrier, etc. from the rear bumper), have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer as soon as possible.</old>
		<new>If Lane Keeping Assist still does not operate normally after cleaning foreign materials (snow, rain, etc.) or removing obstructions (including trailer, carrier, etc. from the rear bumper), have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D0B2FFA95D0E357A37DDB97E8FC9911B8ACF2071DE206AAA8DA0D46EC6BD0D4B">
		<old>When the outside rearview mirror warning light is not working properly, a warning message will appear on the cluster for several seconds and the master warning light (<image/>) will appear on the cluster. If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the outside rearview mirror warning light is not working properly, a warning message will appear on the cluster for several seconds and the master warning light (<image/>) will appear on the cluster. If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="C299B1895D95FC9B72D1601BD5C94788C97D88B39EED508868ADFA3086036AEA">
		<old>If Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist does not operate normally after it is removed, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist does not operate normally after it is removed, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="FCD07E3CD546B54F87BE3A2BF8075C975F7BE3F5BF461BA2226B7734BCB780AA">
		<old>When Safe Exit Warning is not working properly, a warning message will appear on the instrument cluster for several seconds, and the Master warning light (<image/>) will appear on the cluster. If there is a malfunction in Safe Exit Warning, a warning message will be displayed on the instrument cluster display for a certain period, and the Master warning light (<image/>) will turn on. If it does not work properly, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Safe Exit Warning is not working properly, a warning message will appear on the instrument cluster for several seconds, and the Master warning light (<image/>) will appear on the cluster. If there is a malfunction in Safe Exit Warning, a warning message will be displayed on the instrument cluster display for a certain period, and the Master warning light (<image/>) will turn on. If it does not work properly, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="76B61E00E6E64F64F85F630D91B4432A4B092837BF1F6CFD5E0DF513B922E764">
		<old>If Safe Exit Warning does not operate properly after it is removed, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Safe Exit Warning does not operate properly after it is removed, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="092047AC9F7BCBD1B557C23A87D300A106AEEE1160E3AB479A33781AC96519C3">
		<old>If Intelligent Speed Limit Assist does not operate properly after it is removed, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Intelligent Speed Limit Assist does not operate properly after it is removed, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="63BAD12D7DB263357E79A2AEFDCF1381BDF0A3EE51C5FB8E6907D7C4B00C0E66">
		<old>If Driver Attention Warning does not operate properly after obstruction (snow, rain, or foreign material) is removed (including trailer, carrier, etc. from the rear bumper), have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Driver Attention Warning does not operate properly after obstruction (snow, rain, or foreign material) is removed (including trailer, carrier, etc. from the rear bumper), have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="ED655C3AD8362E05DD4694000A907E3A443FF54DA4BB53E3915CE593B9D00102">
		<old>When Blind-Spot View Monitor is not working properly, or the cluster display flickers, or the camera image does not display normally, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Blind-Spot View Monitor is not working properly, or the cluster display flickers, or the camera image does not display normally, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="0A236CDD2D98011463EA4F3617929F93B8AB6AB7E5FC90F4128D221304D39121">
		<old>When Emergency Stop is not working properly, the warning message and Master warning light (<image/>) will appear on the cluster. If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Emergency Stop is not working properly, the warning message and Master warning light (<image/>) will appear on the cluster. If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3C5E9E3DF06EAE1A027FC5AD305E44875A8A077F1E50F370118D9E46EF0A70B1">
		<old>When Rear View Monitor is not working properly, the screen flickers, or the camera image does not display properly, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Rear View Monitor is not working properly, the screen flickers, or the camera image does not display properly, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="2F1F3F43CEE682C1A98B467324853D948672CA239E56812E43516AFC26E067BC">
		<old>If Rear Cross-Traffic Collision-Avoidance Assist does not operate properly after it is removed, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Rear Cross-Traffic Collision-Avoidance Assist does not operate properly after it is removed, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E66B22DBC07137ED65CE8BBF494E787FB193444A8B12EB7AFC816CB7D59CDF5C">
		<old>Do not apply unnecessary force on the wide angle cameras or the ultrasonic sensors. Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist may not operate properly if the wide angle cameras or the ultrasonic sensor(s) are forcibly moved out of proper alignment. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Do not apply unnecessary force on the wide angle cameras or the ultrasonic sensors. Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist may not operate properly if the wide angle cameras or the ultrasonic sensor(s) are forcibly moved out of proper alignment. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="299E16C02D591B5D4554F622FD12036C462123BD0B2A8140BC8E49EEF50E3AF7">
		<old>When Remote Smart Parking Assist is not working properly, the Check Parking Assist warning message will appear on the infotainment system screen. If the message appears, stop using the function, and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Remote Smart Parking Assist is not working properly, the Check Parking Assist warning message will appear on the infotainment system screen. If the message appears, stop using the function, and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1DA3A369832FD806AF693167FBA36F24172AC2057E69DEAD594E1910F583C6EC">
		<old>Remote Smart Parking Assist may not operate normally if the vehicle needs wheel alignment adjustment such as when the vehicle tilts to one side. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Remote Smart Parking Assist may not operate normally if the vehicle needs wheel alignment adjustment such as when the vehicle tilts to one side. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D397394F09E74AAFDAA9B1B5ECA8A81137985866FF9B2C84A497FDFE153EA6B4">
		<old>When Remote Smart Parking Assist is not working properly, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Remote Smart Parking Assist is not working properly, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="4D702DE12526D2FFD80B7D16A0C1035D96D74577892A420EE3ECF9CE01FACF8A">
		<old>If your vehicle does not start after a few attempts, it probably requires servicing. Seek qualified assistance. If the cause of your battery discharging is not apparent, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If your vehicle does not start after a few attempts, it probably requires servicing. Seek qualified assistance. If the cause of your battery discharging is not apparent, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="4038097FE29113EB12759D883BD0205F3B90D71A339B5C71BBA2EDAC85FD6619">
		<old>If the water pump drive belt is broken, or if engine coolant is leaking, stop the engine immediately and call the nearest authorized Kia dealer for assistance.</old>
		<new>If the water pump drive belt is broken, or if engine coolant is leaking, stop the engine immediately and call the nearest authorized Kia dealer for assistance.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="6D6CF68A982089EBC71B0EB2B87216B6AF52F16EA408EC7EB1534EC21F2A951D">
		<old>Proceed with caution, keeping alert for further signs of the engine overheating. If overheating recurs, call an authorized Kia dealer for assistance.</old>
		<new>Proceed with caution, keeping alert for further signs of the engine overheating. If overheating recurs, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="A46DAA1EF017D9F1DFC4AE4180E0E95C9260E44EF8DC2BBA532FBF4F7EAAE7AC">
		<old>If the inverter coolant is running out, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the inverter coolant is running out, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3549AC078E55C7941EFD3003E3F74E9A218211AB5126C51572039C90E42C53CF">
		<old>Serious loss of coolant indicates there is a leak in the cooling system and this should be checked as soon as possible. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Serious loss of coolant indicates there is a leak in the cooling system and this should be checked as soon as possible. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="53440758383D16F4F6437277184537649B1E36871A4812B7FD786733FE092BAC">
		<old>Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer under any of the following circumstances:</old>
		<new>Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer under any of the following circumstances:</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E0AE5A158DF048B604C8BB44E088E54EA8EC789B73424A377A15DAF700D5AAAD">
		<old>Have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer as soon as possible to determine the cause of the problem:</old>
		<new>Have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer as soon as possible to determine the cause of the problem:</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="CB06F2BC1CCA1ED6E078E2FD31331855426C1641EA35DB62D2DF184E4A0073D9">
		<old>If the indicator light does not turn OFF after a few minutes of driving, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the indicator light does not turn OFF after a few minutes of driving, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="19988FD4DE993F20A305967AC739D42189F8537888105EF2D737E69A0525F886">
		<old>Position the wrench as shown in the drawing and tighten the lug nuts. Be sure the socket is seated completely over the nut. Do not stand on the wrench handle or use an extension pipe over the wrench handle. Go around the wheel tightening every other nut until they are all tight. Then double-check each nut for tightness. After changing wheels, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Position the wrench as shown in the drawing and tighten the lug nuts. Be sure the socket is seated completely over the nut. Do not stand on the wrench handle or use an extension pipe over the wrench handle. Go around the wheel tightening every other nut until they are all tight. Then double-check each nut for tightness. After changing wheels, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="A22FD210646ADA51271C4934D9D9CC41F65DB6B35185FE50FEA07E08E1AD0EDA">
		<old>Note that most lug nuts do not have metric threads. Be sure to use extreme care in checking for thread style before installing aftermarket lug nuts or wheels. If in doubt, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Note that most lug nuts do not have metric threads. Be sure to use extreme care in checking for thread style before installing aftermarket lug nuts or wheels. If in doubt, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="606216097708104C8969D299EDFA8817D5C99EB6867FDE8E4A56761277A3D46C">
		<old>If towing is necessary, have your vehicle towed by an authorized Kia dealer or a commercial towing service.</old>
		<new>If towing is necessary, have your vehicle towed by an authorized Kia dealer or a commercial towing service.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B240FD5FE4489278DA7CEF54011620EA27738121D92B3E3AAACBB7D822BFF68F">
		<old>If the deterioration of the engine oil increases depending on the driver’s driving severity, the remaining oil life alert appears on the instrument cluster before the normal engine oil replacement interval. Have the engine oil and filter changed by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the deterioration of the engine oil increases depending on the driver’s driving severity, the remaining oil life alert appears on the instrument cluster before the normal engine oil replacement interval. Have the engine oil and filter changed by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="4387E99C429A80E3244AAB8BEBF7725F284F680EF605149E86D284652343988E">
		<old>If frequent coolant additions are required, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If frequent coolant additions are required, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="75C54ED79B2B27B4E3BECFFD580CF065E084C290716C48EA887AD09F3085897C">
		<old>Have the coolant replaced by an authorized Kia dealer according to the Maintenance Schedule at the beginning of this chapter.</old>
		<new>Have the coolant replaced by an authorized Kia dealer according to the Maintenance Schedule at the beginning of this chapter.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="AB44E106D2D99587AA7AF253E38913B7C5E67F838494296694A8BC1E340C125C">
		<old>In the event the brake system requires frequent additions of fluid, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>In the event the brake system requires frequent additions of fluid, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="721A00EE583D60EA7EAD05F2DD4417B21E0A041E395D58DA13682E8FF960DA0B">
		<old>Contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="83F1CF5D78BD07647653F00362516D9D8672399BBE7407BFB1153866A2431E81">
		<old>For battery related servicing, visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>For battery related servicing, visit an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="715E65295947919CCFF7895DC13D78C223D9ED5E577004AEBE0B7E7D721A5D8F">
		<old>If the replacement fuse blows, this indicates an electrical problem. Avoid using the system involved and immediately consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the replacement fuse blows, this indicates an electrical problem. Avoid using the system involved and immediately consult an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="46EC0BEE0657A6F9E298863DE74910B9F5A4744A55278A7A562B8AC747A108ED">
		<old>Do not remove fuses, relays and terminals fastened with bolts or nuts. The fuses, relays and terminals may not be fastened securely and may cause a fire. If fuses, relays and terminals fastened with bolts or nuts are blown, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Do not remove fuses, relays and terminals fastened with bolts or nuts. The fuses, relays and terminals may not be fastened securely and may cause a fire. If fuses, relays and terminals fastened with bolts or nuts are blown, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="C1F2F103F7DE7B263F5907B8762337522BBE28F050D0EF57D28F98CAD0D729A0">
		<old>If the headlamps or taillamps, stoplights, courtesy lamp or daytime running lights (DRL) do not work and the fuses are <term>OK</term>, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the headlamps or taillamps, stoplights, courtesy lamp or daytime running lights (DRL) do not work and the fuses are <term>OK</term>, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="358D3EBDA17E8C4F035391E33B2ABA8E415BBF769661C5B60AADC5FF715E387F">
		<old>If the multi fuse is blown, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the multi fuse is blown, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1A594F03C44696EB8745CC9C78BD8547BAA0BA68A9F91AA2F753DF2822BB852E">
		<old>If the lamp continues to flicker several times or turns off completely, there may be an error in the vehicle’s electronic control device. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the lamp continues to flicker several times or turns off completely, there may be an error in the vehicle’s electronic control device. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="0A0B49174D4647DCA9E24E86301770C61C833E9BEBAA20E7BC16FC2BCF7C2012">
		<old>You can find moisture inside the lens of lamps after a car wash or driving in the rain. It is a natural event caused by the temperature difference between the inside and the outside of the lamp and does not mean there is a problem with its functions. The moisture inside the lamp will disappear if you drive the vehicle with the headlamp turned on. The level at which the moisture is removed may differ depending on the size/location/condition of the lamp. If moisture still remains inside the lamp, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>You can find moisture inside the lens of lamps after a car wash or driving in the rain. It is a natural event caused by the temperature difference between the inside and the outside of the lamp and does not mean there is a problem with its functions. The moisture inside the lamp will disappear if you drive the vehicle with the headlamp turned on. The level at which the moisture is removed may differ depending on the size/location/condition of the lamp. If moisture still remains inside the lamp, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="F5F8BE1EE41062E7F03E3679875965E73D01A949A36266702A42497FAD26A2B7">
		<old>If you don't have the necessary tools, the correct bulbs or the expertise, consult an authorized Kia dealer. In many cases, it is difficult to replace vehicle light bulbs because other parts of the vehicle must be removed before you can access the bulb. This is especially true if you must remove the headlamp assembly to access the bulb(s).</old>
		<new>If you don't have the necessary tools, the correct bulbs or the expertise, consult an authorized Kia dealer. In many cases, it is difficult to replace vehicle light bulbs because other parts of the vehicle must be removed before you can access the bulb. This is especially true if you must remove the headlamp assembly to access the bulb(s).</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="EB4662BA406552C6EC3F9B388AE1F866D4C23DA7F58CB6712D87EC2BC95C673A">
		<old>If the front lights are not functioning, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the front lights are not functioning, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="DEDFD802CEF6E83C9ECB53E8D8C987DF77DCC90967706053953D9F74E4EB14BB">
		<old>If the side repeater lamp is not functioning, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the side repeater lamp is not functioning, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="C18B1BF98468C0EAE9E978E4F886E7C1D96C741B61C7E2C85159A91713CBD223">
		<old>If the rear lights are not functioning, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the rear lights are not functioning, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="78393F09DF6BE78222DBF5AA398965DF2B7BC2C1A55FF4B496683917ED5EE98A">
		<old>If the interior lights are not functioning, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the interior lights are not functioning, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="81634D648A47F82D435E5D3CC0E9854E392290CD95862C8AF89A323BE66E3BD6">
		<old>If the high-mounted stop lamp (LED) is not functioning, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the high-mounted stop lamp (LED) is not functioning, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="6FA404055A98F54FFFE0190E5853CF88388CCEDB8731FB15D56E956B778B3BD5">
		<old>To ensure the proper function of the emission control systems, have your vehicle inspected and maintained by an authorized Kia dealer according to the maintenance schedule in this manual.</old>
		<new>To ensure the proper function of the emission control systems, have your vehicle inspected and maintained by an authorized Kia dealer according to the maintenance schedule in this manual.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="9B4459A283A88E43B534C93269CE625CC0DAAA8B9A9291FB3F3D9DF5E001012A">
		<old>Before any additional electrical equipment is installed in your vehicle, consult an Authorized Kia Dealer so that you do not void your warranty.</old>
		<new>Before installing any additional electrical equipment in your vehicle, consult an authorized Kia dealer to make sure you don’t void your warranty.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="162C363C813D2E0A5708F99A1FE6B557E09AEACDA132CE14930C37FC81AA6BCA">
		<old>If a mobile two-way radio system is installed improperly, or if an excessively powerful type of system is used, other electronic systems may be adversely affected. To avoid damage to your vehicle, consult an Authorized Kia Dealer concerning proper equipment and installation.</old>
		<new>If a mobile two-way radio system is installed improperly, or if an excessively powerful type of system is used, other electronic systems may be adversely affected. To avoid damage to your vehicle, consult an authorized Kia dealer concerning proper equipment and installation.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="42DCAFFAD903501AFE4B67C30404C67662468E544880C42350842ED5BD8022E7">
		<old>If the seat or seat cover is damaged, have the vehicle checked and repaired by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the seat or seat cover is damaged, have your vehicle inspected and repaired by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="391398BABFFCCDDBFAAAC7A6EE39E8EAF6C55C84F0B85B006E9968CA30ADBDFF">
		<old>Authorized Kia Dealerships provide factory-trained technicians, utilize recommended special service tools and supply genuine Kia replacement parts to help you maintain and service your Kia during your ownership.</old>
		<new>Authorized Kia dealer provide factory-trained technicians, utilize recommended special service tools and supply genuine Kia replacement parts to help you maintain and service your Kia during your ownership.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B4C54F78E648C342EB67F5C4AD09B04DDF1B49FA3B343943FA8AE56E62636891">
		<old>If the EPB does not release normally, load your vehicle onto a flatbed tow truck and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the EPB does not release normally, load your vehicle onto a flatbed tow truck and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="9150319A585CE042B91FC591A09C2B045AED3006DF8C974CF5330E5C1A4ABA58">
		<old>Do not change, alter or adjust the theft-alarm system because it could cause the theft-alarm system to malfunction. In this case, have the checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Do not change, alter or adjust the theft-alarm system because it could cause the theft-alarm system to malfunction. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
		<new>Do not change, alter, or adjust the theft-alarm system in your vehicle. Improper installation of the alarm system could damage the vehicle or cause the system to malfunction.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B4B9C00709BBB282D71E7A02A48206CB59CEB234937D88C3D79DBE7C03855E42">
		<old>If the charging door does not open under certain conditions, such as an electrical malfunction, contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the charging door does not open under certain conditions, such as an electrical malfunction, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="C0322ACDF0D23FAF637DB694E6B338248AED559EE852F56285F88BB5A527762F">
		<old>Should you notice any change in the effort required to steer during normal vehicle operation, have the system checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Should you notice any change in the effort required to steer during normal vehicle operation, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="73F7B5E586983E449E132FB46640732F48CEAE3783674C167B387F962C6AE07C">
		<old>If integrated memory system does not operate normally, have the system checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If integrated memory system does not operate normally, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="72DE5F806BB3328E641201B1BA4C7B2F3780030DC96680737B26B289CE87C5D6">
		<old>If both Power down indicator light and Service warning light illuminate at the same time, visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If both Power down indicator light and Service warning light illuminate at the same time, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="4C1DCBE1DDAC0264B3C4BD281002ADBB768ECF7CEF7733A491200A7A6E6FA999">
		<old>When there is an SRS malfunction. If this happens, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When there is an SRS malfunction. If this happens, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="55A17ED24A911FAD9FD3506731CDD26F2614B1FDBCFBF2D2CD55FC98A2A39901">
		<old>In this case, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>In this case, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3879E5A2D2B2E675312BA5F771A6EE62C35055612B1664D6ABAFC067284C7B2E">
		<old>These 2 warning lights appear at the same time when both the ABS and regular brake system are not working. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>These 2 warning lights appear at the same time when both the ABS and regular brake system are not working. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="99EB3768A899270BC7678AF6ECD7779746F5366212FD2D8434443EAE53F71687">
		<old>When the EPB is malfunctioning. In this case, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the EPB is malfunctioning. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E2BE2ADC96524E8D4561915134FB879BF8A489A99238045B1424E8AD2348BE63">
		<old>When the MDPS is malfunctioning. In this case, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the MDPS is malfunctioning. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="EBBADB4E580AFDD0A852A7D923F0999F212436029BB91E90C8B0D4AA33F4A5B2">
		<old>If this occurs, drive safely and have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Visit an authorized Kia dealer. The operation of the brake pedal may be more difficult than normal and the braking distance may increase.</old>
		<new>If this occurs, drive safely and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. The operation of the brake pedal may be more difficult than normal and the braking distance may increase.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="492587479ACC221FF5C585CC25B9FE7944405ADF4742ABA8A75A60D6A3588F42">
		<old>When the warning light appears while driving, or does not go <term>OFF</term> after starting the vehicle, we recommend that you have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the warning light appears while driving, or does not go <term>OFF</term> after starting the vehicle, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="40AE4E0E3298F19FD4D90C9FAD3188045BF03A02B6192B01F4BDF857DEDD1D0F">
		<old>This warning light remains on after blinking for approximately 60 seconds or repeats blinking on and off at intervals of approximately 3 seconds when the TPMS malfunctions. In this case, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>This warning light remains on after blinking for approximately 60 seconds or repeats blinking on and off at intervals of approximately 3 seconds when the TPMS malfunctions. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="C36E73179B05FD5F21992B8E5AFC0AD63548080586A46F3A8BCDDF3001B48771">
		<old>If the yellow warning light remains on after the sensor has been uncovered or unblocked when you set Forward Safety, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the yellow warning light remains on after the sensor has been uncovered or unblocked when you set Forward Safety, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E69AEB44E74078E6EE305A6C8EA2EEB20216213EF0FC0AE5D2554F86DD5CD1D8">
		<old>When there is an ESC system malfunction. In this case, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When there is an ESC system malfunction. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B66A518E1021FF2D2976F41F3D6E5E575DE83801CD81F01C7D836AC719A30BD9">
		<old>Yellow when there is a malfunction with the Auto Hold system. In this case, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Yellow when there is a malfunction with the Auto Hold system. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3E3A4AA432F0C88181FD50CB5683B0D5987BB1C98A78954A3B9C515F75762AB7">
		<old>In this case, visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>In this case, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3D54A9F10FD2C404EDC68E141385602E7525E13F4E1F4BF8620E520EF68D0EAC">
		<old>If the yellow warning light remains illuminated after the sensor has been uncovered or unblocked when Lane Safety is ON, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer</old>
		<new>If the yellow warning light remains illuminated after the sensor has been uncovered or unblocked when Lane Safety is ON, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer</new>
		<new>If the yellow warning light remains illuminated after the sensor has been uncovered or unblocked when Lane Safety is ON, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="7D2736FF728C77407876F940A2EDDF351793FD44C5FA26D9C0ECA7C1D8E1943A">
		<old>If this occurs, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1DB20E15DE302D200BCFC6B92CC67C925543F0F37135BEE4081356D5B07FC589">
		<old>If the warning appears every time you press the <uicontrol>EV</uicontrol> button, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the warning appears every time you press the <uicontrol>EV</uicontrol> button, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="2002313DE92C7625045DE885A78ACB6382BB668B40FF71A17B4A4B746E4D4711">
		<old>If the head up display needs inspection or repair, visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the head up display needs inspection or repair, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1B6D8B4016B010E1BE9939A5D46617FDC69A34B1F8EA500CEC264E96F7C5D33A">
		<old>When High Beam Assist is not working properly, the <uicontrol>Check High Beam Assist system</uicontrol> warning message displays and the Master warning light (<image/>) illuminates on the instrument cluster. Have the function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When High Beam Assist is not working properly, the <uicontrol>Check High Beam Assist system</uicontrol> warning message displays and the Master warning light (<image/>) illuminates on the instrument cluster. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="EEF89D7074AD836CA66ECFCCD98D978DF062A6CA73F5DC4D767B5C0DBA804BEA">
		<old>If the pretensioner seat belt system is not working properly, this warning light will appear even if there is not a malfunction with the SRS air bag. If the SRS air bag warning light does not appear when the <uicontrol>EV</uicontrol> button has been turned to the <uicontrol>POWER ON</uicontrol> or <uicontrol>DRIVE READY</uicontrol> position, remains illuminated for approximately 3 ~ 6 seconds, or appears while the vehicle is being driven, have an authorized Kia dealer inspect the pretensioner seat belt and SRS air bag system as soon as possible.</old>
		<new>If the pretensioner seat belt system is not working properly, this warning light will appear even if there is not a malfunction with the SRS air bag. If the SRS air bag warning light does not appear when the <uicontrol>EV</uicontrol> button has been turned to the <uicontrol>POWER ON</uicontrol> or <uicontrol>DRIVE READY</uicontrol> position, remains illuminated for approximately 3–6 seconds, or appears while the vehicle is being driven, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="F8D50EC15B34252FB24B381A11C8D91EBDC06AD9CE5D044E9B3313044F4A2F0B">
		<old>Pretensioners are designed to operate only once. After activation, pretensioner seat belts must be replaced. Contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Pretensioners are designed to operate only once. After activation, pretensioner seat belts must be replaced. Contact an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="8C81D045126EE636D4750DCDE45CD5985AFEE94B37D444851F5AB749E80B19A7">
		<old>If your vehicle was flooded and has soaked carpeting or water on flooring, you shouldn't try to start the vehicle; In this situation, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. For cleaning the air bag pad covers, use only a soft, dry cloth or one which has been moistened with plain water. Solvents or cleaners could adversely affect the air bag covers and proper deployment of the system.</old>
		<new>If your vehicle was flooded and has soaked carpeting or water on flooring, you shouldn't try to start the vehicle; In this situation, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. For cleaning the air bag pad covers, use only a soft, dry cloth or one which has been moistened with plain water. Solvents or cleaners could adversely affect the air bag covers and proper deployment of the system.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="94C586332A60163CB71F0A6371DCCC16FE0FC50F0B89BC28ADC48DB4EC348DB9">
		<old>The SRS functions only when the vehicle is in the ON position and remains functional for approximately 3 minutes after the vehicle is turned OFF. If the SRS air bag warning light does not appear or stays on for more than approximately 6 seconds when the vehicle is in the ON position, or if it turns on while driving after the vehicle is started, the SRS is malfunctioning. In this case, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The SRS functions only when the vehicle is in the ON position and remains functional for approximately 3 minutes after the vehicle is turned OFF. If the SRS air bag warning light does not appear or stays on for more than approximately 6 seconds when the vehicle is in the ON position, or if it turns on while driving after the vehicle is started, the SRS is malfunctioning. In this case, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="64B8B60E0D9EFC4E653BE3124D9F746ACDF3F4E2CF2264855520A0F891042A7F">
		<old>Never try to open or repair any components of the curtain air bag system. If necessary, have the system serviced by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Never try to open or repair any components of the curtain air bag system. If necessary, have the system serviced by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="C5BF331602492ABAED06C418C9F8CD84DA2F5331CC072E8958DD9496E936B953">
		<old>If the air bag warning light appears for more than 6 seconds after you turn the <term>EV</term> button to the <term>POWER ON</term> or <term>DRIVE READY</term> position, or if it appears during vehicle operation, an SRS component may not be functioning properly, and you should have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the air bag warning light appears for more than 6 seconds after you turn the <term>EV</term> button to the <term>POWER ON</term> or <term>DRIVE READY</term> position, or if it appears during vehicle operation, an SRS component may not be functioning properly. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
		<new>If the air bag warning light appears for more than 6 seconds after you turn the <term>EV</term> button to the <term>POWER ON</term> or <term>DRIVE READY</term> position, or if it appears during vehicle operation, an SRS component may not be functioning properly, and you should have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3BC6261C20FEB3AAFE5AC76A99C41DBA2765701A34972F022FE404A0F238CD8E">
		<old>If any of the following conditions occurs, this indicates a malfunction of the SRS. Have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If any of the following conditions occurs, this indicates a malfunction of the SRS. Have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
		<new>If any of the following conditions occurs, this indicates a malfunction of the SRS. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="94775C151901AD44CDC50D02E69E9F9AEBDDC097461C97F1A546F2D4DD204066">
		<old>If the release button does not work even after you unlock the all doors, pull the emergency lift cable in the motor room and press the release button on the connector to disconnect it from the vehicle. If the release button still does not work, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the release button does not work even after you unlock the all doors, pull the emergency lift cable in the motor room and press the release button on the connector to disconnect it from the vehicle. If the release button still does not work, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="9E0BAE5F53D9A8BF33B8AFE5F1D6A3D6E041E578BBCA75A21AC874C75F43A1FE">
		<old>If this warning message still displays even when the ambient temperature is high enough, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If this warning message still displays even when the ambient temperature is high enough, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="9186BA87C211CCDC315DC01CFBB7494B9882E87560B5EBCA9F4C4396295F2812">
		<old>If the same problem occurs when you charge the vehicle with a genuine Kia portable charger or other approved external charger, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the same problem occurs when you charge the vehicle with a genuine Kia portable charger or other approved external charger, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="8C9750D2FADD4E85EDDD16D7A3B499D28A99FC4C435134BD26E86BA441FFA601">
		<old>If the same problem occurs when you charge the vehicle with a replacement charging cable or genuine Kia portable charger, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the same problem occurs when you charge the vehicle with a replacement charging cable or genuine Kia portable charger, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
		<new>If the same problem occurs when you charge the vehicle with a genuine Kia portable charger or other approved external charger, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="BB1998DB56EC34C9BDC93ED4A1F06841D2037F582F4248813D89910A59A6AFEC">
		<old>If any leaked liquid comes in contact with your eyes or skin, immediately clean the affected area thoroughly with tap water or saline solution. Then seek medical attention as soon as possible.</old>
		<new>If any leaked liquid comes in contact with your eyes or skin, immediately clean the affected area thoroughly with tap water or saline solution. Then seek medical attention as soon as possible.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="77D646FD03A879680263FAB72BC482B7A8C9C0CB54C6E36A00AE16B701AA92F6">
		<old>If the service interlock connector requires inspection or maintenance, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the service interlock connector requires inspection or maintenance, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="31EF6CD5AB803CF251BF8AF8045A5685161CFAC32EFAD75BBE4073360E2F3B77">
		<old>Painting or applying heat treatment to the vehicle after an accident can reduce the performance of the high voltage battery. If heat treatment is required, contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Painting or applying heat treatment to the vehicle after an accident can reduce the performance of the high voltage battery. If heat treatment is required, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
		<new>Painting or applying heat treatment to the vehicle after an accident can reduce the performance of the high voltage battery. If heat treatment is required, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="9C8F1A1BD774050B98D66BEBD6221CE39D052E583749D19FBC75124262DEB47A">
		<old>If both the update and recovery fail, please contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If both the update and recovery fail, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
		<new>If both the update and recovery fail, contact an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="C29411F946EDAA5DCAE50B3524A94D49F80E564F51983B0546A5F6F00655A036">
		<old>If the airflow from the air vents suddenly decreases, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the airflow from the air vents suddenly decreases, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="28EB3404C1CB3A9A2139605823F20C8B90F3A8F48E5FB31B21211B968DE7A3D6">
		<old>If the steering wheel does not lock properly when you open the driver side door, the warning chime sounds. Try locking the steering wheel again. If that does not solve the problem, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the steering wheel does not lock properly when you open the driver side door, the warning chime sounds. Try locking the steering wheel again. If that does not solve the problem, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="8935273078F176EA265332418534560B28A8C9352B5AE07A6861D898A96012E2">
		<old>If any warning message on the instrument cluster continues to blink, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If any warning message on the instrument cluster continues to blink, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1FA07EA8530F6340182851E9FFB6CB6F6C304CB35E8896C598F35392CF3751B5">
		<old>Be careful not to apply unnecessary force on the radar sensor or sensor cover. If the sensor is forcibly moved out of proper alignment, the smart regeneration system may not operate correctly. A warning message may not be displayed. Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Be careful not to apply unnecessary force on the radar sensor or sensor cover. If the sensor is forcibly moved out of proper alignment, the smart regeneration system may not operate correctly. A warning message may not be displayed. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="56DA3CDCE205CDFFA95B4659B5A9053448F595712AF2C903D07EB339F27CC2EF">
		<old>If the front bumper becomes damaged in the area around the radar sensor, the smart regeneration system may not operate properly. Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the front bumper becomes damaged in the area around the radar sensor, the smart regeneration system may not operate properly. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="67179FED9B96EB131A1ED886391AEFCABDE80E254CC8F45ED1A8C5A7B1A2F745">
		<old>If the system still does not operate normally, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the system still does not operate normally, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="67068C16AF44F095FE25051B2819CBA134129335DA08C2337C252E07132C916B">
		<old>If you do not find any interference and the accelerator pedal is still stuck, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If you do not find any interference and the accelerator pedal is still stuck, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1F5395693782224AF4396937A8079E9D61323C387BD07BF241CC791E58A84B49">
		<old>If you notice a continuous noise or a burning smell when the EPB is used for emergency braking, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If you notice a continuous noise or a burning smell when the EPB is used for emergency braking, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="474DC59A737534F5350C5FDADB42CD538CEEA7B8FE1E0EC178B6B9FF8DC0C7A7">
		<old>If EPB is used for emergency braking, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If EPB is used for emergency braking, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="F629A31D9B8F28BF033EA3703DB7AEF80BD60854525F86288ABAAD46568C9520">
		<old>If the brake warning light remains illuminated after you release the EPB, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the brake warning light remains illuminated after you release the EPB, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="72CB2631EF3ADDDF78EB71D76C5D5C37895BCBF33F929EDF32D20F9498476842">
		<old>If the EPB malfunction indicator appears while you are driving, or does not appear when the vehicle is in <uicontrol>POWER ON</uicontrol> position, this indicates that the EPB may have malfunctioned. Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the EPB malfunction indicator appears while you are driving, or does not appear when the vehicle is in <uicontrol>POWER ON</uicontrol> position, this indicates that the EPB may have malfunctioned. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="5AB93A9D24540A564C76E3A391C0E0C5DEB3B62FA90D5A644A80A576D492761A">
		<old>The EPB warning light may appear if the EPB switch operates abnormally. Turn the vehicle off, then turn it back on after a few minutes. The warning light disappears, and the EPB switch operates normally. If the EPB warning light remains on, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The EPB warning light may appear if the EPB switch operates abnormally. Turn the vehicle off, then turn it back on after a few minutes. The warning light disappears, and the EPB switch operates normally. If the EPB warning light remains on, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="0CCEFC2EED17AC36DA0899A38AD1C8A84EFB071BD473E83DE74EB436932058E3">
		<old>If the EPB warning light blinks, press and then pull up the EPB switch. Press it back into its original position and pull it back up. If the EPB warning light does not turn off, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the EPB warning light blinks, press and then pull up the EPB switch. Press it back into its original position and pull it back up. If the EPB warning light does not turn off, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="33BB15DCBFE46736C801771AA90C69108E9B23C478B510C6EBC911521018EF95">
		<old>If the EPB does not release normally, load your vehicle onto a flatbed tow truck and have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the EPB does not release normally, load your vehicle onto a flatbed tow truck and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="17D2D31774F15F9399A409D82FD9B673813E2491DD94F6A452A3F0E0D13E3EF4">
		<old>If the <uicontrol>AUTO HOLD</uicontrol> indicator light turns yellow, the <uicontrol>AUTO HOLD</uicontrol> function is not working properly. Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the <uicontrol>AUTO HOLD</uicontrol> indicator light turns yellow, the <uicontrol>AUTO HOLD</uicontrol> function is not working properly. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E6A1DC59A3F53500FA4C7F0BE707C1B9A4D04BC9EE3495C4DA196D8106543D1B">
		<old>If there is a malfunction with the driver side door or hood open detection system, the <uicontrol>AUTO HOLD</uicontrol> function may not work properly. Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If there is a malfunction with the driver side door or hood open detection system, the <uicontrol>AUTO HOLD</uicontrol> function may not work properly. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="28DC51288CD092CE6DF2533A5DE7A6F1C772D5FC7E5CADD0970C182FB9CBAAB0">
		<old>To dry the brakes, lightly engage the brake pedal until the braking action returns to normal, taking care to always keep your vehicle under control. If the braking action does not return to normal, stop as soon as it is safe to do so and have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>To dry the brakes, lightly engage the brake pedal until the braking action returns to normal, taking care to always keep your vehicle under control. If the braking action does not return to normal, stop as soon as it is safe to do so and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D035B1CBD4B07BF3C510CBC5D7FEB33D4FA530385DA3B0157970A6120B8C097B">
		<old>The ABS goes through self-diagnosis, and the ABS warning light turns off if everything is normal. If the light stays on, there may be a problem with the ABS. Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The ABS goes through self-diagnosis, and the ABS warning light turns off if everything is normal. If the light stays on, there may be a problem with the ABS. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="171538A439DA461D24103909BE341D9E1C0DE7925823B473BAA72F719BE0490F">
		<old>Restart your vehicle. If the ABS warning light turns off, then your ABS is normal. If it remains on, you may have a problem with the ABS. Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Restart your vehicle. If the ABS warning light turns off, then your ABS is normal. If it remains on, you may have a problem with the ABS. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="5DE8AE3E0177CEEFA6E927208F668F09093204B2285D8C1F34B19D60820385EA">
		<old>The VSM may deactivate even if you do not press the ESC OFF button to cancel VSM operation. This indicates that a malfunction has been detected somewhere in the MDPS system or VSM. If the ESC indicator light or MDPS warning light remains on, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The VSM may deactivate even if you do not press the ESC OFF button to cancel VSM operation. This indicates that a malfunction has been detected somewhere in the MDPS system or VSM. If the ESC indicator light or MDPS warning light remains on, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="A7EC7C2C3D0D94BF9AE27C17C1946CF1743C14D5687B526EF0D1243183423A59">
		<old>If the DBC indicator light turns yellow, the system may have overheated or malfunctioned. If the warning light appears even when the DBC has cooled off, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the DBC indicator light turns yellow, the system may have overheated or malfunctioned. If the warning light appears even when the DBC has cooled off, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="6377F366D3EA2674D6A3653177C9FD3F9AE56F5139B16BC71A5ECB91289F2995">
		<old>Start the vehicle after performing the necessary work like foreign matter removal and waiting 10 minutes. If the pop-up remains up, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Start the vehicle after performing the necessary work like foreign matter removal and waiting 10 minutes. If the pop-up remains up, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E6FEC667FAC202E0D8A74466EE10CDB4287BEF968804984CFDE4483E94B3401B">
		<old>Keeping a vehicle in good operating condition is important to both energy efficiency and safety. Therefore, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Keeping a vehicle in good operating condition is important to both energy efficiency and safety. Therefore, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="490CD35CF870A3F23ADC8568C3476FD83C5FA58978A2DB2CA165E7198E63CED9">
		<old>Winter puts additional burdens on the 12V battery system. Visually inspect the 12V battery and cables as described in the Maintenance section. Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer to inspect your battery to check the level of charge.</old>
		<new>Winter puts additional burdens on the 12V battery system. Visually inspect the 12V battery and cables as described in the Maintenance section. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer to inspect your battery to check the level of charge.</new>
		<new>Winter puts additional burdens on the 12V battery system. Visually inspect the 12V battery and cables as described in the Maintenance section. Have your battery inspected by an authorized Kia dealer to verify the charge level.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="99AE3910D0CEDB919D46D6D0EBE8C630AFAA0CEB6DE631466126EB725928DB8C">
		<old>If the detection sensors have been replaced or repaired, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the detection sensors have been replaced or repaired, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="FDAC32ECB5F4F3A33AD69AAB6208BD28367E2DB522B45C7401BEFF61B3A92DA7">
		<old>If the vehicle experiences an impact to or around the radar, Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist may not operate properly, even if the instrument cluster does not display a warning message. Visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the vehicle experiences an impact to or around the radar, Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist may not operate properly, even if the instrument cluster does not display a warning message. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E5F5CEFF1FA8BED7A7D47AB824A9ECBE88CBE5D8A0F7AEA17FE96D9068DE5C8A">
		<old>You can monitor Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist setting status on the Settings menu of the infotainment system screen. If the Forward Safety warning light (<image/>) or Emergency steering warning light (<image/>) remains ON when Forward safety or Forward/Side safety is selected, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>You can monitor Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist setting status on the Settings menu of the infotainment system screen. If the Forward Safety warning light (<image/>) or Emergency steering warning light (<image/>) remains ON when Forward safety or Forward/Side safety is selected, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="BCD2F30B21B7E34F9E31405CD02C94A6DB818E126D9FD6C76D9348F0ABB27EAD">
		<old>When Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>), the Forward Safety warning light (<image/>), and the Emergency Steering warning light (<image/>) appear on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message that lasts for several seconds. Visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>), the Forward Safety warning light (<image/>), and the Emergency Steering warning light (<image/>) appear on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message that lasts for several seconds. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="BD61819864F51091D66C70AF20C1AF0D2504C307EB4D18CDD5CC42F15C0802AE">
		<old>If Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="09548A7EABD221A02042CBF1313884539E88FA77028B55A6FD78F55AAA86C694">
		<old>If Lane Keeping Assist still does not operate properly after you clean foreign materials (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or remove obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Lane Keeping Assist still does not operate properly after you clean foreign materials (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or remove obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="33D4FECF5D7F638399885C3ED90A7B8896CB2AE6BF027CF3B6B8720D6CBD2B0A">
		<old>When Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message, which lasts for several seconds. If this occurs, have Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message, which lasts for several seconds. If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="649F7E30ABBA958F68B38FB48321F9349D474F822CD94AC4209E188C6FD1B660">
		<old>When the outside rearview mirror warning light is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message, which lasts for several seconds. If this occurs, have Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the outside rearview mirror warning light is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message, which lasts for several seconds. If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D3B51584F0A03E9AF33A35FA07D5C3636022B41E014B98E1CE0884AC50CDA2DC">
		<old>If Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="FC920BCCC7C26E820FFA0A70F0CEF7C37AB744475F57D1AB2FF5E1C8BE983C2C">
		<old>When Safe Exit Warning is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message that lasts for several seconds. If the function does not work properly, visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Safe Exit Warning is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message that lasts for several seconds. If the function does not work properly, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3D4DEE51C491A64B453F47B125E73D9012F657853EF8229E8F7678F83D879ECB">
		<old>If Safe Exit Warning still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Safe Exit Warning still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="0815D4F48AFD6D821DC0BEC9E81C83AE8B5F93483154EA254C1FACF35FC5DF42">
		<old>If Intelligent Speed Limit Assist still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Intelligent Speed Limit Assist still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B4F996776B02E338FCE8E19A8471F3CA3E8AAC245D0A6837F25E0B7C7C4F3CAA">
		<old>If Driver Attention Warning still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Driver Attention Warning still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="49A9608C49713F9242F40B16038D779A97CA2FD3C5F1D23A62845B125445A25C">
		<old>When Smart Cruise Control is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message that lasts for several seconds. Have Smart Cruise Control inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Smart Cruise Control is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message that lasts for several seconds. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="9AF2112379CF2067591ABA265D27A1F37BB4D60374897D939E6AAD304300F33A">
		<old>When Highway Driving Assist is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message that lasts for several seconds. Have Highway Driving Assist inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Highway Driving Assist is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message that lasts for several seconds. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3D7DA6BCA887FB0789BE32BA16B8CA65A1706A592332369815D9A3E1E88575F7">
		<old>Visit an authorized Kia dealer if the Rear View Monitor does not work properly, the screen flickers, or the camera image does not display properly.</old>
		<new>If the Rear View Monitor does not work properly, the screen flickers, or the camera image does not display properly, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="937E12476C8BE855F7850C086FA38C636A498FAD6D09BCE2C948B819999DF7B6">
		<old>Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer if the Surround View Monitor does not work properly, the screen flickers, or the camera image does not display properly.</old>
		<new>If the Surround View Monitor does not work properly, the screen flickers, or the camera image does not display properly, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="75B75D01632E0532D8FD285E4BA9E5AB1939C2313B82B95EEEC4771E04F61E85">
		<old>If Rear Cross-Traffic Collision-Avoidance Assist still does not operate properly after you remove foreign materials (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Rear Cross-Traffic Collision-Avoidance Assist still does not operate properly after you remove foreign materials (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="72997F4E551027D9B4C1891D9C6DC0BB6A7224EA11E2289BF06BB4A72CFBC742">
		<old>You can check the contents of the warning in the service message of the utility information view of the instrument cluster. If the function still does not work properly, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>You can check the contents of the warning in the service message of the utility information view of the instrument cluster. If the function still does not work properly, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="9B3132C2006D7969FA63ADF452F883090E21CFA1AA22A1071B4C7670ACB5E5C9">
		<old>The ultrasonic sensors detect objects around your vehicle. Parking Distance Warning may be temporarily limited or may not operate if snow, rain, foreign substances, and so on cover the sensor. You can check the detection sensor blind warning target (ultrasonic sensor) in the service message of the utility information view in the instrument cluster. Parking Distance Warning works normally if you remove the contamination from the recognition sensor. Always keep it clean. If the function still does not work properly even after you remove the contamination, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The ultrasonic sensors detect objects around your vehicle. Parking Distance Warning may be temporarily limited or may not operate if snow, rain, foreign substances, and so on cover the sensor. You can check the detection sensor blind warning target (ultrasonic sensor) in the service message of the utility information view in the instrument cluster. Parking Distance Warning works normally if you remove the contamination from the recognition sensor. Always keep it clean. If the function still does not work properly even after you remove the contamination, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B331129775B03D1146E6940AE54442E1FC9B2E87D39115DBC9D7750DACC1CC5A">
		<old>If Parking Distance Warning does not operate properly, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Parking Distance Warning does not operate properly, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="2DC6842229BBF6FE579B5A5C55EA8D6EF0935140F3BCB248133BB87C0886C81F">
		<old>If there is a problem with Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist or related functions and parts, a warning message displays on the instrument cluster. If the function still does not work properly, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If there is a problem with Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist or related functions and parts, a warning message displays on the instrument cluster. If the function still does not work properly, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1B7E60EBBEB77F99FD77BA9E07C3DFF2EBEBC11BCF0333136E57B15BDBC0C09E">
		<old>The wide-rear view camera and rear ultrasonic sensors detect objects around your vehicle. Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist may be temporarily limited or may not operate if snow, rain, foreign substances, and so on obscure the sensor. You can check the detection sensor blind warning target (wide-rear view camera and rear ultrasonic sensor) in the service message of the utility information view in the instrument cluster. Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist works normally if you remove the contamination from the recognition sensor. Always keep it clean. If the function still does not work properly even after you remove the contamination, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The wide-rear view camera and rear ultrasonic sensors detect objects around your vehicle. Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist may be temporarily limited or may not operate if snow, rain, foreign substances, and so on obscure the sensor. You can check the detection sensor blind warning target (wide-rear view camera and rear ultrasonic sensor) in the service message of the utility information view in the instrument cluster. Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist works normally if you remove the contamination from the recognition sensor. Always keep it clean. If the function still does not work properly even after you remove the contamination, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="4335936B2FCD55E6643FF867FC9F1CF41002B10AA54521524A98EE66378C2DAF">
		<old>Do not apply unnecessary force to the Wide Rear View camera or ultrasonic sensors. Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist may not operate properly if you forcibly move the Wide Rear View camera or ultrasonic sensors out of proper alignment. If Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist does not operate properly, visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Do not apply unnecessary force to the Wide Rear View camera or ultrasonic sensors. Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist may not operate properly if you forcibly move the Wide Rear View camera or ultrasonic sensors out of proper alignment. If Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist does not operate properly, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="32906B999E92ED9AB870D0DC6C594B8E2C9BAC7A7DEAA3D1E00DCEC9B8AD7319">
		<old>When Remote Smart Parking Assist is not working properly, the <uicontrol>Check Parking Assist</uicontrol> warning message will appear on the infotainment system screen. If the message appears, stop using the function, and have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Remote Smart Parking Assist is not working properly, the <uicontrol>Check Parking Assist</uicontrol> warning message will appear on the infotainment system screen. If the message appears, stop using the function, and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="695A15E610B2AAD55D863163E89EB06B024279E9AA052C570BA4494AD1A9E411">
		<old>If it is not obvious why your battery was discharged, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If it is not obvious why your battery was discharged, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3817229D6DBED9DCD2891EA094804705918D7F215672975324DEF19A22C705EA">
		<old>Try to restart your vehicle. If your vehicle does not restart, contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Try to restart your vehicle. If your vehicle does not restart, contact an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="98028D9DA724FAF0B6BE96E689A585C6A6CAF5510A354300E96517B644AAD713">
		<old>Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer under any of the following circumstances:</old>
		<new>Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer under any of the following circumstances:</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="33F94023DD360EF23E5882A78DAC68DCBA5E1277C96D60D50C6B1F8FA52E1562">
		<old>Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer as soon as possible to determine the cause of the problem:</old>
		<new>Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer to determine the cause of the problem:</new>
		<new>Have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer as soon as possible to determine the cause of the problem:</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="A331F2D9EC3424ACC9AE8EC62F3B3F4C739E29DE7BDB10790F1DEE2180F9CF54">
		<old>If the indicator light does not turn OFF after a few minutes of driving, visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the indicator light does not turn OFF after a few minutes of driving, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="21E57610A59B483C90F32B2E55808047CED695D325821355A271239A62A5A8E2">
		<old>When you use the TMK, the tire pressure sensors and wheel may be stained by sealant. Remove the tire pressure sensors and wheel stained by the sealant and have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When you use the TMK, the tire pressure sensors and wheel may be stained by sealant. Remove the tire pressure sensors and wheel stained by the sealant and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="CCF48A1E1FA0FBE207767943EA77E4F55D4324CC9699E99D71E0DD58E0E583F3">
		<old>If the disabled vehicle is unable to be moved, do not forcibly continue the towing. We recommend that you contact an authorized Kia dealer or a commercial tow truck service for assistance.</old>
		<new>If the disabled vehicle is unable to be moved, do not forcibly continue the towing. Contact an authorized Kia dealer or a commercial tow truck service for assistance.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="5A5DD5489C2AFF1A155BAC0ECFE5F43EF8D8193260A16CA486B0A3045EFBD77F">
		<old>Performing maintenance work on a vehicle can be dangerous. You can be seriously injured while performing some maintenance procedures. If you lack sufficient knowledge and experience or the proper tools and equipment to do the work, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Performing maintenance work on a vehicle can be dangerous. You can be seriously injured while performing some maintenance procedures. If you lack sufficient knowledge and experience or the proper tools and equipment to do the work, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="ADF33D07C55F97EACA09B40FFDA861086BD6142088035C8A67936CC294774E94">
		<old>Improper owner maintenance during the warranty period may affect warranty coverage. For details, read the separate Warranty &amp; Maintenance book provided with the vehicle. If you're unsure about any servicing or maintenance procedure, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Improper owner maintenance during the warranty period may affect warranty coverage. For details, read the separate Warranty &amp; Maintenance book provided with the vehicle. If you're unsure about any servicing or maintenance procedure, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="87676EBC4FC2C25AFF3B2497EB3B071D29D7C6D2372359A4F0F0C1309AABD394">
		<old>When replacing or adding coolant, visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Have the coolant replaced or added by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D091D2A5A74D16E4CFFCBB50F7CB6DB9EE36643448D76306724DE5323A0AA0AB">
		<old>In the event the brake system requires frequent additions of fluid, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>In the event the brake system requires frequent additions of fluid, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="F84AD7D4AF15E7B93DE2A8F304666CECEFDC47119CE943DEA05488B2CABD809E">
		<old>When the message 'Refill coolant' displayed on cluster, stop driving and have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the message 'Refill coolant' displayed on cluster, stop driving and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B82D9E11FA9A8D943B2AE8F13914D8D72FF329F81F7947A198C9CBF0FCF33385">
		<old>If the brake system requires you to add fluid frequently, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the brake system requires you to add fluid frequently, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="BC6493B0527EED7DDEFD7473E386E9A66E88B444E3A3159C790DFE5911534D5E">
		<old>Your vehicle is equipped with a maintenance-free battery. If your vehicle’s battery is marked with LOWER and UPPER on the side, you can check the electrolyte level. The electrolyte level should be between the LOWER and UPPER marks. If the electrolyte level is low, add distilled (demineralized) water. (Never add sulfuric acid or other electrolytes.) When refilling, be careful not to splash the battery and adjacent components. Do not overfill the battery cells, as this can cause corrosion on other parts. Make sure to tighten the cell caps. Contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Your vehicle is equipped with a maintenance-free battery. If your vehicle’s battery is marked with LOWER and UPPER on the side, you can check the electrolyte level. The electrolyte level should be between the LOWER and UPPER marks. If the electrolyte level is low, add distilled (demineralized) water. (Never add sulfuric acid or other electrolytes.) When refilling, be careful not to splash the battery and adjacent components. Do not overfill the battery cells, as this can cause corrosion on other parts. Make sure to tighten the cell caps. Contact an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="BBF8BC7BD421728DFFCAE70400804930C22B91B81D73B795CBA0789DCD8ECF77">
		<old>If you receive a warning message on the instrument cluster or a malfunction alert text on your phone, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If you receive a warning message on the instrument cluster or a malfunction alert text on your phone, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="0BF6797C457BF297E76B6EE51DD1D0D65150453D62C6AFA0104E64CC1C4D2A99">
		<old>If the tire sustains impact, inspect the tire’s condition or contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the tire sustains impact, have the tire inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="CE7798C864036549F381040D04440CCAC32C9DEB4A2981F5EE53DB753440593E">
		<old>If a replacement fuse blows, this indicates an electrical problem. Avoid using the respective system and immediately consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If a replacement fuse blows, this indicates an electrical problem. Avoid using the respective system and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="17A83BAC2DFE6067550531C88427F301C6053E6932C79573B068244FBFBCA810">
		<old>Do not remove fuses, relays, and terminals fastened with bolts or nuts. The fuses, relays, and terminals may be fastened incompletely and could cause a possible fire. If fuses, relays, and terminals fastened with bolts or nuts are blown, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Do not remove fuses, relays, and terminals fastened with bolts or nuts. The fuses, relays, and terminals may be fastened incompletely and could cause a possible fire. If fuses, relays, and terminals fastened with bolts or nuts are blown, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="A59976927D4CC87F78F0DBD4F5126E6D7AFCD277042CCD967939A579320A59CE">
		<old>If the new fuse does not fit tightly, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the new fuse does not fit tightly, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="F23F5A2F9CBA1FB4AFCA27CD522D76ACFB5BCDDFCE52EC20656C3BF3A8AC30C6">
		<old>If the headlamps, tail lamps, brake lamps, courtesy lamp, or daytime running lights (DRL) do not work and their fuses are not blown, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the headlamps, tail lamps, brake lamps, courtesy lamp, or daytime running lights (DRL) do not work and their fuses are not blown, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="8A064525C08DAF9FFCE89F54C4ECB4162DCEE8C2133C1FCCBDDC5BE2F9717E98">
		<old>If the multi-fuse is blown, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the multi-fuse is blown, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="6A9045B5F4F8C82485D9CE460F3A0BFC64ABD26C5E6BFBE32D3094E974527E8A">
		<old>The electronic system may not function correctly, even when the motor room and internal fuse box’s individual fuses are not disconnected. In this case, the main fuse (BFT type), which is inside the positive battery terminal (+) cap, may be disconnected and causing the malfunction. Because the main fuse is designed more intricately than other parts, you should visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The electronic system may not function correctly, even when the motor room and internal fuse box’s individual fuses are not disconnected. In this case, the main fuse (BFT type), which is inside the positive battery terminal (+) cap, may be disconnected and causing the malfunction. Because the main fuse is designed more intricately than other parts, have it serviced by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="02C7B42E774FE31D8C58D2E4F188D39B33B245E28A9F57DDBEADD2938790C29B">
		<old>If the high-mounted stop lamp (LED) is not functioning, please have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. The LED lamp cannot be replaced as a single unit because it is an integrated component. Instead, the entire LED lamp unit must be replaced. It’s essential to have a skilled technician check or repair the high-mounted stop lamp (LED) to prevent any damage to related vehicle parts.</old>
		<new>If the high-mounted stop lamp (LED) is not functioning, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. The LED lamp cannot be replaced as a single unit because it is an integrated component. Instead, the entire LED lamp unit must be replaced. It’s essential to have a skilled technician check or repair the high-mounted stop lamp (LED) to prevent any damage to related vehicle parts.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="EC59F916A296AD4EEBC1A97501D3556AC5ECA84860B321288C501A79EA00430E">
		<old>If the front lights are not functioning, pleasehave your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the front lights are not functioning, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3718F363D5C612829A2A93635AD61A0468809D30C5C594E5175CE4CE8811843C">
		<old>If the rear/side lights are not functioning, please have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the rear/side lights are not functioning, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="2ED13D990930258CBD943E6BF6004DF329D24F7D95D3E4FAD0B2F2B7A05E0534">
		<old>In case of matte paint finish vehicles, it is impossible to modify only the damaged area and repair of the whole part is necessary. If the vehicle is damaged and painting is required, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer. Take extreme care, as it is difficult to restore the quality after the repair.</old>
		<new>In case of matte paint finish vehicles, it is impossible to modify only the damaged area and repair of the whole part is necessary. If the vehicle is damaged and painting is required, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. Take extreme care, as it is difficult to restore the quality after the repair.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="2A1CD09A08E3A7C0E03B87A4B97B2D9EF0BDEC7ADCE65D2A36046384700EC3C8">
		<old>If the AWD warning light (<image/>) remains illuminated on the instrument cluster, your vehicle may have an AWD system malfunction. When the AWD warning light (<image/>) appears, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the AWD warning light (<image/>) remains illuminated on the instrument cluster, your vehicle may have an AWD system malfunction. When the AWD warning light (<image/>) appears, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="A12F91C1A3DCF7ECD1BB537F6C98D2392FBA8B93839B578B930BFBE78DD8AB6D">
		<old>Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer</old>
		<new>Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="DEC34611E2DC4A253CC144A26CD7B7E59ABA2BE6ED0FC9A0F08DCC801F48299B">
		<old>When Electronically Controlled Suspension (ECS) with Road Preview is not working properly, the warning message will appear on the instrument cluster. If this occurs, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer <?oxy_comment_start author="june" timestamp="20250814T161854+0900" comment="북미 BER 문구 have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer."?>. <?oxy_comment_end?></old>
		<new>When Electronically Controlled Suspension (ECS) with Road Preview is not working properly, the warning message will appear on the instrument cluster. If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer <?oxy_comment_start author="june" timestamp="20250814T161854+0900" comment="북미 BER 문구 Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer."?>. <?oxy_comment_end?></new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="F97BC32E52BB121D95202CCB4DA5EEE9190DFA2A17136B6CAFAFC0F3C95BD015">
		<old>Do not change, alter or adjust the immobilizer system because it could cause the immobilizer system to malfunction. In this case, have the checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Do not change, alter or adjust the immobilizer system in your vehicle. Improper installation of the alarm system could damage the vehicle or cause the system to malfunction.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D4424B0359F6D2FAAD0666299F74F233B62A357806BC067E98036A22C369B275">
		<old>If this occurs, have the system checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If this occurs, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="FFB3950FBA4A6D4329BF5DBC6F6D01C50AF47E393C5F3332FF0B31A133A1EE86">
		<old>If both Power down warning light and Service warning light illuminate at the same time, visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If both Power down warning light and Service warning light illuminate at the same time, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="28AB08E049EB0B157C5F897746B633172BA0BF858DECCF2E98250845B27FFA91">
		<old>If this occurs, drive safely and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. Visit an authorized Kia dealer. The operation of the brake pedal may be more difficult than normal and the braking distance may increase.</old>
		<new>If this occurs, drive safely and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. The operation of the brake pedal may be more difficult than normal and the braking distance may increase.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="5807ADFFB4609CCFC1390A04BCB0BC0B02E9B9C50D57D69BFBA4472ADD2ECBF2">
		<old>When the warning light appears while driving, or does not go <term>OFF</term> after starting the vehicle, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the warning light appears while driving, or does not go <term>OFF</term> after starting the vehicle, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="FEB01AFE60C85C5A4016A35D9FFE3C695D2331CB8868F0F8FEE95E0649FA6E6F">
		<old>When the head up display needs inspection or repair, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the head up display needs inspection or repair, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="F63914E6D0101B80CF40732025453DE5A03C1A1174727943E50622EE01933120">
		<old>When High Beam Assist is not working properly, the warning message will appear and (<image/>) warning light will appear on the cluster. In this case, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When High Beam Assist is not working properly, the warning message will appear and (<image/>) warning light will appear on the cluster. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B646C45F1702F56C094FF388A362CD14BD26C69BE487D78D5ADE6310A2EFB97D">
		<old>If High Beam Assist still does not operate properly after cleaning foreign materials (snow, rain, etc.) or removing obstructions (including trailer, carrier, etc. from the rear bumper), have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If High Beam Assist still does not operate properly after cleaning foreign materials (snow, rain, etc.) or removing obstructions (including trailer, carrier, etc. from the rear bumper), have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="5668972060CF5228406E47D9659432E09F35563EB621724C03CA68FF50AA6D0F">
		<old>If the SRS air bag warning light remains illuminated while the vehicle is being driven, have the vehicle checked and repaired by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the SRS air bag warning light remains illuminated while the vehicle is being driven, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1FEEC4FA9109174EEA2570DFD7B7D03B09B66189ACEFB4EDD2445D84335C75C3">
		<old>Air bags can only be used once–have an authorized Kia dealer replace the air bag immediately after deployment.</old>
		<new>Air bags can only be used once–have the system replaced by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="47C0CEF9EBD5C8B16F05CB01D9873AFE584BB15C14542AF93497D95A5F636862">
		<old>If the installation location or angle of the sensors is altered in any way, the air bags may deploy when they should not or they may not deploy when they should, causing severe injury or death. Therefore, do not try to perform maintenance on or around the air bag sensors. Have the vehicle checked and repaired by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the installation location or angle of the sensors is altered in any way, the air bags may deploy when they should not or they may not deploy when they should, causing severe injury or death. Therefore, do not try to perform maintenance on or around the air bag sensors. Have the system serviced by an autrhozied Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="2C3177D1A49401FF5F2C465FC8E961A58908AE99DBA9AE07A1399929C1E749EC">
		<old>If the seat or seat cover is damaged, have the vehicle checked and repaired by an authorized Kia dealer. Inform the dealer that your Kia is equipped with side air bags and an ODS.</old>
		<new>If the seat or seat cover is damaged, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. Inform the dealer that your Kia is equipped with side air bags and an ODS.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D0E513EC5C0E31E6147F057DA98B272CFF393FBA162894F8CE29FC61378B6EEF">
		<old>If the installation location or angle of the sensors is altered in any way, the air bags may deploy when they should not or they may not deploy when they should. Do not try to perform maintenance on or around the air bag sensors. Have the vehicle checked and repaired by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the installation location or angle of the sensors is altered in any way, the air bags may deploy when they should not or they may not deploy when they should. Do not try to perform maintenance on or around the air bag sensors. Have the system serviced by an autrhozied Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="CC40E512FB52022CB872BFBD4090F810BD2CBAEC1F2E57576A065B235C1FCC6D">
		<old>Changing the sensor installation angles due to deformation of the front bumper, front end module, body, or front doors where side collision sensors are installed may cause problems. Have the vehicle checked and repaired by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Changing the sensor installation angles due to deformation of the front bumper, front end module, body, or front doors where side collision sensors are installed may cause problems. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="2D7C9F6058A52EA71CBD0C81C7CD4563E6D278F18DBEB974B26A649B30BFA048">
		<old>If the SRS air bag warning light does not appear, or continuously remains on, have your vehicle immediately inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the SRS air bag warning light does not appear, or continuously remains on, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="179AE121AF6B16482646ECB1568633B8D47EE66F1ED5A3A1DF4EDFF5519FB18B">
		<old>When the high voltage components or the high voltage battery requires inspection or maintenance, have the function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the high voltage components or the high voltage battery requires inspection or maintenance, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D375429EC2B1AF7B93C0898B213433D003168EDC934709D7C5168BE63A1FAE6E">
		<old>If the charge capacity and distance to empty suddenly or dramatically decline, have the function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the charge capacity and distance to empty suddenly or dramatically decline, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="8695E01956156A94FB5E4EB24E4083FA2D3293A39982A6C89C0CBE50F0A53031">
		<old>If the vehicle is in a collision, have the function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the vehicle is involved in a collision, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer to verify that the high voltage battery is still connected.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E3C4BC00F73B479060AA35DB4C0377499F3167D4F4C2276224ED297486B41CD7">
		<old>If V2L does not operate properly when you connect electronic devices, have the function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If V2L does not operate properly when you connect electronic devices, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="DC155DB736B8F25BC0C3A77C2FDFEAD43083E9722EA7A52576A828415E97247F">
		<old>When the warning light appears while driving, or does not go <term>OFF</term> after starting the vehicle, have the function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the warning light appears while driving, or does not go <term>OFF</term> after starting the vehicle, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="329BD4CF5172B930CA0796C7212B8B676DB8E338EA8ACBDC9F3057094E470014">
		<old>If this occurs, drive safely and have the function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. The operation of the brake pedal may be more difficult than normal and the braking distance may increase.</old>
		<new>If this occurs, drive safely and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. The operation of the brake pedal may be more difficult than normal and the braking distance may increase.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="47BDDAC6923FFD0C03F372EC690A2E255E129A98B9525D5A9E44221FBF23D3A7">
		<old>Do not drive the vehicle when this warning message displays. Park the vehicle in a safe location, then have it towed to the nearest authorized Kia dealer to be inspected.</old>
		<new>Do not drive the vehicle when this warning message displays. If this occurs, park the vehicle in a safe location. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="F2C48B6FD35B2593391A0B3ACE6F46C96165428A74D4C053849AFACB5B17C09D">
		<old>If this warning message still displays even after the EV button has been in the OFF position long enough, do not drive the vehicle and have it inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If this warning message still displays even after the EV button has been in the OFF position long enough, do not drive the vehicle and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="6603DFFE09206833BEC20EAF1FC164DE7C84348CEC93F7DC4AD43F768E4F030D">
		<old>If this occurs, park the vehicle in a safe location and have it towed to the nearest authorized Kia dealer to be inspected.</old>
		<new>If this occurs, park the vehicle in a safe location. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="C1A71F4171AEFDF869049CD3B568B3CDD2D0561E571F3E63351CAC5F1723BB02">
		<old>If the Electronic Parking Brake (EPB) does not release normally, take your vehicle to an authorized Kia dealer by loading the vehicle on a flatbed tow truck and have the system checked.</old>
		<new>If the Electronic Parking Brake (EPB) does not release normally, load your vehicle onto a flatbed tow truck and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D60418C683E06E8B0AD7465B67933C320C71F80ACA20825B007A66B0CE8494DD">
		<old>The service interlock connector, located within the motor compartment, is a safety device that disables the high voltage of the battery. Have you vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The service interlock connector, located within the motor compartment, is a safety device that disables the high voltage of the battery. It’s for vehicle inspections at an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="7ED9F0729B3374A24B2BF58ABCE4C5E948CF17024AC1A58D56E8461482B7638C">
		<old>If you need to inspect or maintain the service interlock connector, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If you need to inspect or maintain the service interlock connector, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="67892A3C2E21F4D36CFD37AED2F53518B4CF3CF3800049BC16DEACDD046F9EB5">
		<old>When you visit an authorized Kia dealer for repairs due to a failure of the fingerprint authorization system related parts, your registered fingerprint might be deleted. Have your smart key checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When you visit an authorized Kia dealer for repairs due to a failure of the fingerprint authorization system related parts, your registered fingerprint might be deleted. Have your smart key with you when you visit an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="AF05960F7749A67FAA45DE3E8BCAAD0C3189E4CCD597C83AC177B0F0480CE274">
		<old>Pet Mode may deactivate due to a malfunction in the high-voltage battery or the parking brake. If there is a malfunction in the high-voltage battery or the parking brake, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Pet Mode may deactivate due to a malfunction in the high-voltage battery or the parking brake. If there is a malfunction in the high-voltage battery or the parking brake, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="C8F3C65787CCC12A4646ADD4662BB06E4EA1E0718930CDE7043295104EBCF384">
		<old>Since laws vary, the requirements for towing trailers, cars, or other types of vehicles or apparatus may differ. Ask an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Since laws vary, the requirements for towing trailers, cars, or other types of vehicles or apparatus may differ. Consult an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B1BD0083250C4C32869249784C8691A6828FEB353DE86A86170AB33BF178980F">
		<old>Have an authorized Kia dealer assist with installing the wiring harness.</old>
		<new>Have the wiring harness installed by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="92ABEEF10C4A8A7E1A9B73BDA7D8EB66F705B60434BD5578D2A8727AAE91CF27">
		<old>Visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="CA5170485721BBCBE87EB462E57194C8072746583381BE78AE187F28E0C731A7">
		<old>When Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist is not working properly, the warning message will appear, and the yellow (<image/>), (<image/>) and (<image/>) warning lights will appear on the cluster. Visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist is not working properly, the warning message will appear, and the yellow (<image/>), (<image/>) and (<image/>) warning lights will appear on the cluster. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="8498BCA15E25B77D765E0E337BCA77FF4C415FB2544641528F2AEFA3C391A357">
		<old>If Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist does not operate properly after obstruction (snow, rain, or foreign material) is removed (including trailer, carrier, etc. from the rear bumper), visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="F6D368C2CB25F8B3AA484341AE645B8202515CBAFBA26382FC5DB27AE243D122">
		<old>If Lane Keeping Assist still does not operate properly after cleaning foreign materials (snow, rain, etc.) or removing obstructions (including trailer, carrier, etc. from the rear bumper), have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer as soon as possible.</old>
		<new>If Lane Keeping Assist still does not operate properly after you clean foreign materials (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or remove obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3F8465A83A303FBFC7DBDC0082BDF21FE9C93E3AAFF29FCA9E1D76172DAC4B9F">
		<old>If this occurs, have Lane Following Assist be inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="CCD865414AE6F739AEEF52040AFBC062E0CCBA7AE7D7E3361B39991BD6503C9E">
		<old>If the detection sensor or the area near the sensor has been damaged or impacted in any way, Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist may not operate properly, even if a warning message does not appear on the instrument cluster. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the detection sensor or the area near the sensor has been damaged or impacted in any way, Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist may not operate properly, even if a warning message does not appear on the instrument cluster. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="F671979E8DDF59D184620492700F539F03A0F8AD7565F8AB2B3D03A327D542B6">
		<old>If this occurs, have Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist be inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="AB9349DEC4F1CC15023441D243E2A72757D77D17A904F4747BF09C5482F4C828">
		<old>When the outside rearview mirror warning light is not working properly, the warning message will appear on the cluster for several seconds, and the master (<image/>) warning light will appear on the cluster. If this occurs, have Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist be inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the outside rearview mirror warning light is not working properly, the warning message will appear on the cluster for several seconds, and the master (<image/>) warning light will appear on the cluster. If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1260716B2318974C882F2B53819F27FDDAF8B25AA1B9F09C1313FB95D7B223B9">
		<old>If Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist does not operate properly after it is removed, have Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist be inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist does not operate properly after it is removed, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="0C4CE3E3360C7682D9C692DECA81C9EC75EDFF7C02D47D50F17007E70BAC2459">
		<old>When Safe Exit Assist is not working properly, the warning message will appear on the cluster for several seconds, and the Master (<image/>) warning light will appear on the cluster. If there is a malfunction in Safe Exit Assist, a warning message will be displayed on the cluster display for a certain period, and the Master warning light (<image/>) will turn on. If it does not work properly, visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Safe Exit Assist is not working properly, the warning message will appear on the cluster for several seconds, and the Master (<image/>) warning light will appear on the cluster. If there is a malfunction in Safe Exit Assist, a warning message will be displayed on the cluster display for a certain period, and the Master warning light (<image/>) will turn on. If it does not work properly, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3903B4C126B6CDB548DFA3F4E855A9589D3321F728EF6EDEC37D6DF2C76CDF91">
		<old>Have Safe Exit Assist be inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="7BF780C0FC4FCF15FDF60C1322DABBAA15AF5D7186B6589E9AC90C6345C823D4">
		<old>If Safe Exit Assist does not operate properly after it is removed, visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Safe Exit Assist does not operate properly after it is removed, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="32F3A111BBEAF3746BF1CBE450ED9128798EF2812CD38B9726071581C3F7A371">
		<old>When Blind-Spot View Monitor does not work properly, the instrument cluster display flickers, or the camera image does not display normally, have Blind-Spot View Monitor inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Blind-Spot View Monitor does not work properly, the instrument cluster display flickers, or the camera image does not display normally, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1A195D22DF0B64FE48145F029A7D98DD11CD4914961F9F1AD78489BC90EF3857">
		<old>If this occurs, have Driver Attention Warning inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="513FF0BE263A856C2AE4D0AB1FFC48BA4E3F074ECE144D4DA28C281AB5E0C7E9">
		<old>When <uicontrol>Emergency Stop</uicontrol> is not working properly, the warning message and Master warning light (<image/>) will appear on the cluster. If this occurs, have the function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When <uicontrol>Emergency Stop</uicontrol> is not working properly, the warning message and Master warning light (<image/>) will appear on the cluster. If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="BCA04518E5D575DF4CE65EC43C8356E1BC0A723AFAF21AF86551EE3FF6D51C2C">
		<old>If there is a problem with the Highway Lane Change Assist function, you cannot change the settings and should have the function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If there is a problem with the Highway Lane Change Assist function, you cannot change the settings and should have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="61E2DC80598AF4F8B2D3A0DA7861E54A89ED00342DE53085016F161AB69E5F02">
		<old>Have the function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="827ACBA9F63079BD783A1B5414743B250E8AA1AC2E3B80C38D244AAC3ABAAFD0">
		<old>You can check the Parking Distance Warning status in the service message of the utility information view of the instrument cluster. If it still does not work properly, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>You can check the Parking Distance Warning status in the service message of the utility information view of the instrument cluster. If it still does not work properly, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="F4FD958B0586BC40DD2E4D82EADD8E26E73E274F124A98343E2EF7F7F1A0DD13">
		<old>The ultrasonic sensors detect objects around your vehicle. Parking Distance Warning may be temporarily limited or may not operate if snow, rain, foreign substances, and so on cover on the sensor. You can check the detection sensor blind warning target (ultrasonic sensor) in the service message of the utility information view in the instrument cluster. Parking Distance Warning should work normally if you remove the contamination from the recognition sensor. Always keep it clean. If the function still does not work properly even after you remove the contamination, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The ultrasonic sensors detect objects around your vehicle. Parking Distance Warning may be temporarily limited or may not operate if snow, rain, foreign substances, and so on cover on the sensor. You can check the detection sensor blind warning target (ultrasonic sensor) in the service message of the utility information view in the instrument cluster. Parking Distance Warning should work normally if you remove the contamination from the recognition sensor. Always keep it clean. If the function still does not work properly even after you remove the contamination, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="350315B0F2E4AC95F50EF191C9BE9FCE46AE41F9C3B2B5AB4A673034594E0FB1">
		<old>If it still does not work properly even after you have removed the contamination, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If it still does not work properly even after you have removed the contamination, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="31A3380E75A5A74D5EBCFC6E1DB573605C8CA712275107527A6AF9D071D7AA34">
		<old>The wide view camera, and ultrasonic sensors detect objects around the vehicle. Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist may be temporarily limited or may not operate if snow, rain, foreign substances, etc. get on the sensor. Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist works normally if you remove the contamination from the recognition sensor. Always keep it clean. If it still does not work properly even after you have removed the contamination, visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The wide view camera, and ultrasonic sensors detect objects around the vehicle. Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist may be temporarily limited or may not operate if snow, rain, foreign substances, etc. get on the sensor. Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist works normally if you remove the contamination from the recognition sensor. Always keep it clean. If it still does not work properly even after you have removed the contamination, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="59141290CE7A339B0D16EF52CE35DB8438C44DFD50C363073BCEE0D5F47EF8B4">
		<old>Do not apply unnecessary force on the wide angle cameras or the ultrasonic sensors. Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist may not operate properly if the wide angle cameras or the ultrasonic sensor(s) is forcibly moved out of proper alignment. Visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Do not apply unnecessary force to the Wide Rear View camera or ultrasonic sensors. Parking Collision- Avoidance Assist may not operate properly if you forcibly move the Wide Rear View camera or ultrasonic sensors out of proper alignment. If Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist does not operate properly, have your vehicle inspeced by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1080BD1B6A490F5B6B2A9F6D42733F9F873D5A0E54BC1B2F4871440A4A1E8BB1">
		<old>Please contact the nearest Kia dealership if the tire cannot be made roadworthy with the Tire Mobility Kit.</old>
		<new>Contact the nearest Kia dealer if the tire cannot be made roadworthy with the Tire Mobility Kit.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="053CE23414BD8F7AF579279AADA461C28C77A21A29260BBC532930BBCFF5252C">
		<old>When you use the TMK with a sealant that is not approved by Kia, the tire pressure sensors may be damaged by that sealant. Approved sealant on the tire pressure sensor and wheel should be removed when you replace the tire and the tire pressure sensors should be inspected at an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When you use the TMK with a sealant that is not approved by Kia, the tire pressure sensors may be damaged by that sealant. Approved sealant on the tire pressure sensor and wheel should be removed when you replace the tire and have the tire pressure sensors inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="292320E188F73C81DBBC815ECDC3FFF1CF1D1DBCABDDF0B2BEA68D11DB2FF204">
		<old>When replacing or adding coolant, visit an authorized Kia dealer. For your convenience, it can be replaced prior to it’s interval when you do maintenance of other items.</old>
		<new>Have the coolant replaced or added by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner. For your convenience, it can be replaced prior to it’s interval when you do maintenance of other items.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="BA8EDCB78A70BC111B0EA8DD20D2B1179F64187735B30621A287AFBC9A231D21">
		<old>When the “Refill coolant” message is displayed on cluster, stop driving and have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the “Refill coolant” message is displayed on cluster, stop driving and have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="4B64BF58B4B9D720237B8DFB7C59C89714459E825D9136952F94DDD1C4A93A7D">
		<old>However, if the lamp continues to flicker several times or turns off completely, there may be an error in the vehicle’s electronic control device. In this case, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer immediately.</old>
		<new>However, if the lamp continues to flicker several times or turns off completely, there may be an error in the vehicle’s electronic control device. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="58E3BF82625E9EEFB7CE4E1CF7829A068D25C6D17F9AAB6B078489D19E9ADBDE">
		<old>If the interior wooden trim is damaged, you may get a splinter from the wood surface. Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the interior wooden trim is damaged, you may get a splinter from the wood surface. Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3B72B7841E49D6EE71341BB1D0E709B8474DD9FDC0F6AC7CD198462194F92191">
		<old>Note that most lug nuts do not have metric threads. Be extremely careful and check the thread style before you install aftermarket lug nuts or wheels. If in doubt, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Note that most lug nuts do not have metric threads. Be extremely careful and check the thread style before you install aftermarket lug nuts or wheels. If in doubt, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="295BFEBD9EB304325E4ECB887ED66EBD01B3B1CC4BE2E2C822FF682238B5E27C">
		<old>If there are safety risks, such as fuel flow restriction, surging, loss of power, hard starting problems, and so on, replace the fuel filter immediately regardless of the maintenance schedule. Consult an authorized Kia dealer for details.</old>
		<new>If there are safety risks, such as fuel flow restriction, surging, loss of power, or hard starting problems, replace the fuel filter immediately regardless of the maintenance schedule. Consult an authorized Kia dealer for details.</new>
	</pair>
</pairs>