<pairs>
	<pair hash="A29B7DD1B3C837D673FA10B89EDA5E6DA1886D63B836E5D4757553C1F9866494">
		<old>as-is</old>
		<new>to-be</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="0AA94CCCF780C578E8FE772E95ED2FA2F846BE602463FD723753F2DE10F29C99">
		<old>Never add any fuel system cleaning agents to the fuel tank other than what has been specified. Consult an authorized Kia dealer for details.</old>
		<new>Never add any fuel system cleaning agents to the fuel tank other than what has been specified. Consult a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="4242E614B12C72055FE3ABEA568BD307D4092AC8DA3CA0A52B2A331240FF6491">
		<old>Contact an authorized Kia dealer for more details.</old>
		<new>Contact a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="4845FDDB28217FC5E5DA693E464E9F4B512858B4B164211D4700534D3A909B9F">
		<old>When the smart key does not work correctly, try the spare, or open and close the door with the mechanical key. When your smart key does not work correctly, contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the smart key does not work correctly, try the spare, or open and close the door with the mechanical key. When your smart key does not work correctly, contact a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="868DD52C897DFE347F14EFE98ECC8C5BE19EFD5B676E1E424CF55B8C21449D3F">
		<old>If you are unsure how to use or replace the battery, contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If you are unsure how to use or replace the battery, contact a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="9D6E3A8A8C6158B2C93C851B49114FE149D646DFCB0E3B787E697BC549324B3A">
		<old>To replace your smart key, visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>To replace your smart key, contact a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="9150319A585CE042B91FC591A09C2B045AED3006DF8C974CF5330E5C1A4ABA58">
		<old>Do not change, alter or adjust the theft-alarm system because it could cause the theft-alarm system to malfunction. In this case, have the checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Do not change, alter or adjust the theft-alarm system because it could cause the theft-alarm system to malfunction. In this case, have the system serviced by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="25D70A6CBFDC6409463F606EA9AA002640521B7CBD271951BB00A1FA36CE4C29">
		<old>If you want this feature deactivated, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If you want this feature deactivated, consult a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="CAE1133A04DCF876696D7656172F88C163298CF6F2DBAA1BF0E2DD15105133E5">
		<old>If you lose your keys, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If you lose your keys, contact a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="F97BC32E52BB121D95202CCB4DA5EEE9190DFA2A17136B6CAFAFC0F3C95BD015">
		<old>Do not change, alter or adjust the immobilizer system because it could cause the immobilizer system to malfunction. In this case, have the checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Do not change, alter or adjust the immobilizer system because it could cause the immobilizer system to malfunction. In this case, have the system serviced by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D4424B0359F6D2FAAD0666299F74F233B62A357806BC067E98036A22C369B275">
		<old>If this occurs, have the system checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If this occurs, have the system inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="545BE56A997AE12B430FBEE616C81944E8510FD8F00CB79A728C559DA820AFD3">
		<old>Do not modify or repair any part of the power liftgate by yourself. This must be done by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Do not modify or repair any part of the power liftgate by yourself. This must be done by an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="54F7EFEA4989A175E16B0CFCEE12279F91B3CD7F25F64033DA33660BAC8A4851">
		<old>If the power liftgate does not operate properly after you perform the preceding procedure, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the power liftgate does not operate properly after you perform the preceding procedure, have the system inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="F25FE1DA54403C8009241C3754099D0DD1EE9629C667EC853EA058CA2A49E2DA">
		<old>If the fuel filler door does not open under certain conditions, such as an electrical malfunction, contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the fuel filler door does not open under certain conditions, such as an electrical malfunction, contact a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="8684C69DE18B0E9912B372B713F1F49C83C5EBB1126FE98BC9BB94D9139C6662" status="same">
		<old>Even small amounts of the wrong fuel could result in damage to the fuel system and the engine. Have the system serviced by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Even small amounts of the wrong fuel could result in damage to the fuel system and the engine. Have the system serviced by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="C0322ACDF0D23FAF637DB694E6B338248AED559EE852F56285F88BB5A527762F">
		<old>Should you notice any change in the effort required to steer during normal vehicle operation, have the system checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Should you notice any change in the effort required to steer during normal vehicle operation, have the system inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="0BDA21F1182F97C2CE5B2B69A7E089547F518B8C0A81F7E06384219FB76E76EA">
		<old>If the EPS system does not work or an error occurs, the warning light on the instrument panel may turn on or blink, and it may require more force to operate the steering wheel. Hold the steering wheel more tightly than usual and operate with greater force. Then immediately pull your vehicle over to a safe place and have it inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the EPS system does not work or an error occurs, the warning light on the instrument panel may turn on or blink, and it may require more force to operate the steering wheel. Hold the steering wheel more tightly than usual and operate with greater force. Then immediately pull your vehicle over to a safe place and have it inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="AFFCE68F2634B58F642DE45E04767B01EF458608D5275E6D813AAD6B378B2FF3">
		<old>Do not subject the camera to a strong impact as this could cause a malfunction. If this happens, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer as soon as possible.</old>
		<new>Do not subject the camera to a strong impact as this could cause a malfunction. If this happens, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="73F7B5E586983E449E132FB46640732F48CEAE3783674C167B387F962C6AE07C">
		<old>If integrated memory system does not operate normally, have the system checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If integrated memory system does not operate normally, have the system inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="4C1DCBE1DDAC0264B3C4BD281002ADBB768ECF7CEF7733A491200A7A6E6FA999">
		<old>When there is an SRS malfunction. If this happens, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When there is an SRS malfunction. If this happens, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="4439FE6E84D448CD3801B941DF1A53ED71E9D373B3DA32D4A3E00C28FE9BAED6">
		<old>Have your vehicle towed to and inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Have your vehicle towed to and inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="A30A1498EACC12264FCB6A4E71751AF9B24FBE89DE514FAC63D09B1B08622A5F">
		<old>Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="95F0382A7C4966C94530E3D85BD48613F2DC39E782AD42B6880C9AFCE254757A" status="multi">
		<old>Have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3879E5A2D2B2E675312BA5F771A6EE62C35055612B1664D6ABAFC067284C7B2E">
		<old>These 2 warning lights appear at the same time when both the ABS and regular brake system are not working. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>These 2 warning lights appear at the same time when both the ABS and regular brake system are not working. In this case, your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="0335C2D33B3B33C80E60292902C59C4369855646D09597AAC55B838F7AEB9C63">
		<old>Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer as soon as possible.</old>
		<new>Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D21A725C62BFD09D13D296DFE36AB87AA008B322BBA32553BF4595B08911A33B">
		<old>When the <term>EPB</term> is malfunctioning. In this case, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the <term>EPB</term> is malfunctioning. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E2BE2ADC96524E8D4561915134FB879BF8A489A99238045B1424E8AD2348BE63">
		<old>When the MDPS is malfunctioning. In this case, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the MDPS is malfunctioning. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="55A17ED24A911FAD9FD3506731CDD26F2614B1FDBCFBF2D2CD55FC98A2A39901">
		<old>In this case, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>In this case, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="86E017475DF82A6B679D3161653372AF90BD760D7FF397005F02CCE0F990BCE2">
		<old>Whenever there is a malfunction with the emission control system, engine, or vehicle powertrain. Have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Whenever there is a malfunction with the emission control system, engine, or vehicle powertrain. Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="4C4D15ECDE46E7C330F790F870E83F06EA2AE8D11E5FA4F653EF519DE119BC15">
		<old>If the MIL appears, catalytic converter damage is possible, which could result in loss of engine power and accordingly vehicle speed is reduced. In this case, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the MIL appears, catalytic converter damage is possible, which could result in loss of engine power and accordingly vehicle speed is reduced. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="569E28870E2DB9CD8EAB9AC19C6CACD1DC1A36C6F287FF5807629F746A6BB62B">
		<old>If the warning light remains on after you add oil, or if oil is not available, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. Continuing to drive with the warning light on may cause engine failure.</old>
		<new>If the warning light remains on after you add oil, or if oil is not available, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner. Continuing to drive with the warning light on may cause engine failure.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="ACFC9A0A2F3442B00BB39B7397ACC0A5B588B98536F7134FCD78C1F37407BA99">
		<old>If this warning light blinks despite following the above procedure (at this time, the LCD warning message will display), have the GPF system checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If this warning light blinks despite following the above procedure (at this time, the LCD warning message will display), have the GPF system inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="40AE4E0E3298F19FD4D90C9FAD3188045BF03A02B6192B01F4BDF857DEDD1D0F">
		<old>This warning light remains on after blinking for approximately 60 seconds or repeats blinking on and off at intervals of approximately 3 seconds when the TPMS malfunctions. In this case, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>This warning light remains on after blinking for approximately 60 seconds or repeats blinking on and off at intervals of approximately 3 seconds when the TPMS malfunctions. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="C36E73179B05FD5F21992B8E5AFC0AD63548080586A46F3A8BCDDF3001B48771">
		<old>If the yellow warning light remains on after the sensor has been uncovered or unblocked when you set Forward Safety, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the yellow warning light remains on after the sensor has been uncovered or unblocked when you set Forward Safety, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="A7E4880E8FB47524C9D8819343751DFEEEDB24994870DB40CB27CE4FECCC0F0D">
		<old>If the warning light remains on after the sensor has been uncovered or unblocked when Forward/Side Safety is on, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the warning light remains on after the sensor has been uncovered or unblocked when Forward/Side Safety is on, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="241D0758C8E56D785B7DB663676A121E1491D805225E8385351A3BCF8BFEBAEB">
		<old>When Forward Attention Warning is disabled or a malfunction is detected. If the warning light remains on after the in-cabin camera has been uncovered or unblocked, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Forward Attention Warning is disabled or a malfunction is detected. If the warning light remains on after the in-cabin camera has been uncovered or unblocked, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E69AEB44E74078E6EE305A6C8EA2EEB20216213EF0FC0AE5D2554F86DD5CD1D8">
		<old>When there is an ESC system malfunction. In this case, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When there is an ESC system malfunction. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B66A518E1021FF2D2976F41F3D6E5E575DE83801CD81F01C7D836AC719A30BD9">
		<old>Yellow when there is a malfunction with the Auto Hold system. In this case, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Yellow when there is a malfunction with the Auto Hold system. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="49B3E25F3B73B2635E82A76B0F4F2E494E1F0F4D4BFE8DFCE1674E24454AA170">
		<old>This indicator light appears for 2 seconds then disappears when the vehicle cannot detect the smart key in the vehicle and the <term>ENGINE START/STOP</term> button is <term>ON</term>. In this case, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>This indicator light appears for 2 seconds then disappears when the vehicle cannot detect the smart key in the vehicle and the <term>ENGINE START/STOP</term> button is <term>ON</term>. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="61ACCDB91625309A4237C4BB6983A440553F67DDC9EF112F1557640344697870">
		<old>When the immobilizer system is malfunctioning. In this case, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the immobilizer system is malfunctioning. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B626C8709F5FA437DBEAF0AF74CB93DCCDD1A3BC10D6D3BF1D6A3166EB64430C">
		<old>The turn signal system may be malfunctioning and should be inspected by an authorized Kia dealer if the indicator light does any of the following:</old>
		<new>The turn signal system may be malfunctioning and should be inspected by an authorized Kia dealer or service partner if the indicator light does any of the following:</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="58EFE67992C88793D52C6CF90750E83C39B73FFEA9F3AD7BFAEF311B3A969C0A">
		<old>If the yellow warning light remains illuminated after the sensor has been uncovered or unblocked when Lane Safety is <term>ON</term>, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer</old>
		<new>If the yellow warning light remains illuminated after the sensor has been uncovered or unblocked when Lane Safety is <term>ON</term>, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3BF32CC3C4ACDE4DBB76765BFA522A11F1C4E3605632F4AB03DC5980FBD0609E">
		<old>In this case, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>In this case, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="59CE0B57D592E95FE081226520A0FE70F1336192E77E8354E6F89276A43C2F4A">
		<old>If the indicator light remains yellow after you have uncovered or unblocked the front view camera, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the indicator light remains yellow after you have uncovered or unblocked the front view camera, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="2DE8F4D13138F2CF661D12128CFCB16A9B899EEDE5B5B3A7AF6E932D2EED57C1">
		<old>This warning message appears when the remaining engine oil life reaches 1% or below. Replace the engine oil immediately through an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>This warning message appears when the remaining engine oil life reaches 1% or below. Have the engine oil replaced by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="870A90D153C6A3957D8DDC1BFDA595DAC110966DC818D9162513852B08996D3F">
		<old>If the warning continues after you disconnect external electrical devices, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the warning continues after you disconnect external electrical devices, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="37CC87BDFD911321C60DF9FB2453AC28EDA9FFE310B9413F9DD89B7C7B972551">
		<old>If the warning appears every time you press the <term>ENGINE START/STOP</term> button, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the warning appears every time you press the <term>ENGINE START/STOP</term> button, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="2002313DE92C7625045DE885A78ACB6382BB668B40FF71A17B4A4B746E4D4711">
		<old>If the head up display needs inspection or repair, visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the head up display needs inspection or repair, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="16A248A3C4ACB38D320BEA7D60E6DA6A3513E03675B672B2D1F21499E42E5217">
		<old>When High Beam Assist is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message that lasts for several seconds. Have the function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When High Beam Assist is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message that lasts for several seconds. Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="12229E1D93FB915A3A604705CAFBC6D5C6E269D4861C4DCB09C221E9E29C43C1">
		<old>If a communication malfunction occurs in the wiper system and the wipers do not operate normally, set the wiper switch to the <term>LO</term> position. The wipers will operate at a constant <term>LO</term> speed. If this occurs, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If a communication malfunction occurs in the wiper system and the wipers do not operate normally, set the wiper switch to the <term>LO</term> position. The wipers will operate at a constant <term>LO</term> speed. If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B8B5EFBE467DD9922BA68FBBC937D947148E65D65E0A8D4B1715EF9E4FA42A64">
		<old>If the pretensioner seat belt system is not working properly, this warning light will appear even if there is not a malfunction with the SRS air bag. If the SRS air bag warning light does not appear when the <term>ENGINE START/STOP</term> button has been turned to the <term>ON</term> position, remains illuminated for approximately 3 ~ 6 seconds, or appears while the vehicle is being driven, have an authorized Kia dealer inspect the pretensioner seat belt and SRS air bag system as soon as possible.</old>
		<new>If the pretensioner seat belt system is not working properly, this warning light will appear even if there is not a malfunction with the SRS air bag. If the SRS air bag warning light does not appear when the <term>ENGINE START/STOP</term> button has been turned to the <term>ON</term> position, remains illuminated for approximately 3–6 seconds, or appears while the vehicle is being driven, have the system inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="F8D50EC15B34252FB24B381A11C8D91EBDC06AD9CE5D044E9B3313044F4A2F0B">
		<old>Pretensioners are designed to operate only once. After activation, pretensioner seat belts must be replaced. Contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Pretensioners are designed to operate only once. After activation, pretensioner seat belts must be replaced. Contact a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1405E25DBF3A3B16A3A0C14B8B111A3BDA38882881392F966CCC04A7598904DA">
		<old>If the SRS airbag warning light remains illuminated while the vehicle is being driven, have the vehicle checked and repaired by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the SRS airbag warning light remains illuminated while the vehicle is being driven, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="2E32AF248A8C289F40C2E6533EED2C1A590049E6753C66EDD30F605F946C1C0F">
		<old>Air bags can only be used once– have an authorized Kia dealer replace the air bag immediately after deployment.</old>
		<new>Air bags can only be used once– have the system replaced by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="A0DA95EA2D1B93857438C32041D72DE00761DD8ED2DAC71B4C819E6E600FC331">
		<old>If your vehicle was flooded and has soaked carpeting or water on flooring, you shouldn't try to start the vehicle; In this situation, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. For cleaning the airbag pad covers, use only a soft, dry cloth or one which has been moistened with plain water. Solvents or cleaners could adversely affect the airbag covers and proper deployment of the system.</old>
		<new>If your vehicle was flooded and has soaked carpeting or water on flooring, you shouldn't try to start the vehicle; In this situation, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner. For cleaning the airbag pad covers, use only a soft, dry cloth or one which has been moistened with plain water. Solvents or cleaners could adversely affect the airbag covers and proper deployment of the system.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="5432B087E80F77027A0AF29AC12F29E95FF11E2316C739539974332B76389F3E">
		<old>If the installation location or angle of the sensors is altered in any way, the airbags may deploy when they should not or they may not deploy when they should, causing severe injury or death. Therefore, do not try to perform maintenance on or around the airbag sensors. Have the vehicle checked and repaired by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the installation location or angle of the sensors is altered in any way, the airbags may deploy when they should not or they may not deploy when they should, causing severe injury or death. Therefore, do not try to perform maintenance on or around the airbag sensors. Have the system serviced by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1EE009063F2FDA322A3CF1FF4E533A5E6E4B8FFDBC22CE87A92C8FF420EDF634">
		<old>Do not tamper with or disconnect wiring or other components of the SRS system, including the addition of any kind of badges to the pad covers or modifications to the body structure. Doing so could adversely affect SRS performance and lead to possible injury. If necessary, have the system serviced by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Do not tamper with or disconnect wiring or other components of the SRS system, including the addition of any kind of badges to the pad covers or modifications to the body structure. Doing so could adversely affect SRS performance and lead to possible injury. If necessary, have the system serviced by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="DE1114D74FC6FC3B83F30B981A2E56116837614750264F956E862DC116BAC64E">
		<old>SRS and pre-tensioners contain explosive chemicals. If you scrape a vehicle without removing the SRS and pre-tensioners, it may cause a fire. Before scraping a vehicle, contact an authorized Kia dealer</old>
		<new>SRS and pre-tensioners contain explosive chemicals. If you scrape a vehicle without removing the SRS and pre-tensioners, it may cause a fire. Before scraping a vehicle, contact a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="402F0B231C1434C1E2C0E04513BA65CF0D9209381F16E5CBF092FC64C926194B">
		<old>The SRS functions only when the vehicle is in the <term>ON</term> position and remains functional for approximately 3 minutes after the vehicle is turned <term>OFF</term>. If the SRS airbag warning light does not appear or stays on for more than approximately 6 seconds when the vehicle is in the <term>ON</term> position, or if it turns on while driving after the vehicle is started, the SRS is malfunctioning. In this case, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The SRS functions only when the vehicle is in the <term>ON</term> position and remains functional for approximately 3 minutes after the vehicle is turned <term>OFF</term>. If the SRS airbag warning light does not appear or stays on for more than approximately 6 seconds when the vehicle is in the <term>ON</term> position, or if it turns on while driving after the vehicle is started, the SRS is malfunctioning. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="11BB92768AB02C7B62746F912D6C28A13308B5A633625AB444B43643018779B2">
		<old>Never try to open or repair any components of the curtain airbag system. If necessary, have the system serviced by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Never try to open or repair any components of the curtain airbag system. If necessary, have the system serviced by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="38EA6EBC383BDC7681C556BF63851298329F5097063A1D08827C47916E57A727">
		<old>Problems may arise if you change the sensor installation angles due to deformation of the front bumper, body, or B pillar where the side collision sensors are installed. In this case, have the system serviced by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Problems may arise if you change the sensor installation angles due to deformation of the front bumper, body, or B pillar where the side collision sensors are installed. In this case, have the system serviced by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="0867F6E12D4E87908577DF08DF8CE5108D4A846B69E1D24B833E3D456AA041AB">
		<old>If the air bag warning light appears for more than 6 seconds after you turn the <term>ENGINE START/STOP</term> button to the <term>ON</term> position, or if it appears during vehicle operation, an SRS component may not be functioning properly, and you should have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the air bag warning light appears for more than 6 seconds after you turn the <term>ENGINE START/STOP</term> button to the <term>ON</term> position, or if it appears during vehicle operation, an SRS component may not be functioning properly. Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="783DED1E3C0AC36867A76A382478426EB6EE77828AC1A20D29CEC3EE5C3B6D4F">
		<old>If any of the following conditions occur, this indicates a malfunction in the air bag system. Have an authorized Kia dealer inspect the air bag system as soon as possible.</old>
		<new>If any of the following conditions occur, this indicates a malfunction in the air bag system. Have the system inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3BC6261C20FEB3AAFE5AC76A99C41DBA2765701A34972F022FE404A0F238CD8E">
		<old>If any of the following conditions occurs, this indicates a malfunction of the SRS. Have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If any of the following conditions occurs, this indicates a malfunction of the SRS. Have the system inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="42DCAFFAD903501AFE4B67C30404C67662468E544880C42350842ED5BD8022E7">
		<old>If the seat or seat cover is damaged, have the vehicle checked and repaired by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the seat or seat cover is damaged, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="875B1E99BB713857DB1A3007974747080722F007DE4BBC6F5A21BCD7932891E6">
		<old>If the installation location or angle of the sensors is altered in any way, the air bags may deploy when they should not or they may not deploy when they should. Do not perform maintenance on or around the air bag sensors. Have the vehicle checked and repaired by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the installation location or angle of the sensors is altered in any way, the air bags may deploy when they should not or they may not deploy when they should. Do not perform maintenance on or around the air bag sensors. Have the system serviced by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="CC40E512FB52022CB872BFBD4090F810BD2CBAEC1F2E57576A065B235C1FCC6D">
		<old>Changing the sensor installation angles due to deformation of the front bumper, front end module, body, or front doors where side collision sensors are installed may cause problems. Have the vehicle checked and repaired by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Changing the sensor installation angles due to deformation of the front bumper, front end module, body, or front doors where side collision sensors are installed may cause problems. Have the vehicle checked and repaired by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="2D7C9F6058A52EA71CBD0C81C7CD4563E6D278F18DBEB974B26A649B30BFA048">
		<old>If the SRS air bag warning light does not appear, or continuously remains on, have your vehicle immediately inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the SRS air bag warning light does not appear, or continuously remains on, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="9C8F1A1BD774050B98D66BEBD6221CE39D052E583749D19FBC75124262DEB47A">
		<old>If both the update and recovery fail, please contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If both the update and recovery fail, contact a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1BA06EF1B479D5A481B1874A5A27E5FAC19853FFDF68F9183458A9EBD32B071A">
		<old>At this time, replace the climate control filter. If you find it challenging to do so yourself, have the climate control filter replaced by an authorized Kia dealer. For details on how to replace the climate control air filter, refer to <xref/>.</old>
		<new>At this time, replace the climate control filter. If you find it challenging to do so yourself, have the climate control filter replaced by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner. For details on how to replace the climate control air filter, refer to <xref/>.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="C29411F946EDAA5DCAE50B3524A94D49F80E564F51983B0546A5F6F00655A036">
		<old>If the airflow from the air vents suddenly decreases, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the airflow from the air vents suddenly decreases, have the system inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="97EF3E1DF31F066915409A54F317D715DE2D53FD2C1CB2AC019309100FB75D8A">
		<old>If abnormal operation occurs, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If abnormal operation occurs, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="11BC4C2433A2F8C53DB483BA4629B6F079D1B25997DFC2E851A171E4CC55D654">
		<old>If necessary, contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If necessary, contact a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="64947F4A8E2D37427C2629C108F24360F6531C03644A0468260983FE8386695B">
		<old>If you hear a change in the sound of the exhaust, or if you drive over something that strikes the underbody of the vehicle, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If you hear a change in the sound of the exhaust, or if you drive over something that strikes the underbody of the vehicle, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="28EB3404C1CB3A9A2139605823F20C8B90F3A8F48E5FB31B21211B968DE7A3D6">
		<old>If the steering wheel does not lock properly when you open the driver side door, the warning chime sounds. Try locking the steering wheel again. If that does not solve the problem, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the steering wheel does not lock properly when you open the driver side door, the warning chime sounds. Try locking the steering wheel again. If that does not solve the problem, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1C2E6E8C33529C505DE9470637B94B2A3197200974051315649BD711E2B51522">
		<old>If there is a transmission failure, the gear position indicator on the instrument cluster blinks, and your vehicle may not move. If this happens, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If there is a transmission failure, the gear position indicator on the instrument cluster blinks, and your vehicle may not move. If this happens, have the system inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D270CC445850421D23B7DC5192B85CFE13B3D405096DE5973D337F0EB12D84A5">
		<old>If the warning message still appears, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the warning message still appears, have the system inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="04C994522B3FA38322DFB41266B25CBAD37B6B47AB7AA34B3A342E5768E78866">
		<old>If the warning message still appears, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer to prevent unexpected accidents.</old>
		<new>If the warning message still appears, have the system inspected by a professional workshop to prevent unexpected accidents. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="8935273078F176EA265332418534560B28A8C9352B5AE07A6861D898A96012E2" status="multi">
		<old>If any warning message on the instrument cluster continues to blink, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If any warning message on the instrument cluster continues to blink, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="CA29FEB83CFD674BF905B67399AB9F88EF8F93F4CF0AF6F01E343E483AF9BA45">
		<old>When Ground View Monitor is not working properly, the screen flickers, or the camera image does not display normally, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the Ground View Monitor does not work properly, the screen flickers, or the camera image does not display properly, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="67068C16AF44F095FE25051B2819CBA134129335DA08C2337C252E07132C916B">
		<old>If you do not find any interference and the accelerator pedal is still stuck, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If you do not find any interference and the accelerator pedal is still stuck, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="5C22E4E03A1695CC0CECC03A36922C9CEB41EEA0EC7F07EA237B7F15B03A95B9">
		<old>If <term>EPB</term> is used for emergency braking, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If <term>EPB</term> is used for emergency braking, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="19A5A52B3F20694C741EDC1F1B1E4CFE33486679BCB6EFB65F63461E676112EC">
		<old>If the brake warning light remains illuminated after you release the <term>EPB</term>, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the brake warning light remains illuminated after you release the <term>EPB</term>, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="90AEC19DB5ED1AD4081CAC7D6B99B3803D77A79DE88CE4790FAD89934B5EE949">
		<old>If the <term>EPB</term> malfunction indicator appears while you are driving, or does not appear when the vehicle is in <term>ON</term> position, this indicates that the <term>EPB</term> may have malfunctioned. Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the <term>EPB</term> malfunction indicator appears while you are driving, or does not appear when the vehicle is in <term>ON</term> position, this indicates that the <term>EPB</term> may have malfunctioned. Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E530ED9E2B358D8AC5970B84FEDBD675C11B1459D838E15A9505B37BDF34FF15">
		<old>The <term>EPB</term> warning light may appear if the <term>EPB</term> switch operates abnormally. Turn the engine off, then turn it back on after a few minutes. The warning light disappears, and the <term>EPB</term> switch operates normally. If the <term>EPB</term> warning light remains on, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The <term>EPB</term> warning light may appear if the <term>EPB</term> switch operates abnormally. Turn the engine off, then turn it back on after a few minutes. The warning light disappears, and the <term>EPB</term> switch operates normally. If the <term>EPB</term> warning light remains on, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D51B919EA1AB0AADAEBF86010A3E0F3001D8C6633BA7DC9D2C0CE1D9EEB6C57E">
		<old>If the <term>EPB</term> warning light blinks, press and then pull up the <term>EPB</term> switch. Press it back into its original position and pull it back up. If the <term>EPB</term> warning light does not turn off, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the <term>EPB</term> warning light blinks, press and then pull up the <term>EPB</term> switch. Press it back into its original position and pull it back up. If the <term>EPB</term> warning light does not turn off, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="F37F36ABCEE198CA99650FF245609C829833B84B31FEEF3950541D15EF433F9A">
		<old>If the <term>EPB</term> does not release normally, load your vehicle onto a flatbed tow truck and have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the <term>EPB</term> does not release normally, load your vehicle onto a flatbed tow truck and have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="0E1F91F8DAAA61DBED24AAC3890A799DE56586DB15C38EF3EA057F635BF6640C">
		<old>If the <term>AUTO HOLD</term> indicator light turns yellow, the <term>AUTO HOLD</term> function is not working properly. Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the <term>AUTO HOLD</term> indicator light turns yellow, the <term>AUTO HOLD</term> function is not working properly. Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="85D1601C03FA9141257BC93EF45BF8C884100179605ABC8F4C6AD008B3523C91">
		<old>If there is a malfunction with the driver side door or hood open detection system, the <term>AUTO HOLD</term> function may not work properly. Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If there is a malfunction with the driver side door or hood open detection system, the <term>AUTO HOLD</term> function may not work properly. Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="511EDD268B5466F64C8276B967B80B968096AD0E88774E590BEBD5E6C3789875">
		<old>To dry the brakes, lightly engage the brake pedal until the braking action returns to normal, taking care to always keep your vehicle under control. If the braking action does not return to normal, stop as soon as it is safe to do so and visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>To dry the brakes, lightly engage the brake pedal until the braking action returns to normal, taking care to always keep your vehicle under control. If the braking action does not return to normal, stop as soon as it is safe to do so and have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D035B1CBD4B07BF3C510CBC5D7FEB33D4FA530385DA3B0157970A6120B8C097B">
		<old>The ABS goes through self-diagnosis, and the ABS warning light turns off if everything is normal. If the light stays on, there may be a problem with the ABS. Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The ABS goes through self-diagnosis, and the ABS warning light turns off if everything is normal. If the light stays on, there may be a problem with the ABS. Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="171538A439DA461D24103909BE341D9E1C0DE7925823B473BAA72F719BE0490F">
		<old>Restart your vehicle. If the ABS warning light turns off, then your ABS is normal. If it remains on, you may have a problem with the ABS. Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Restart your vehicle. If the ABS warning light turns off, then your ABS is normal. If it remains on, you may have a problem with the ABS. Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="9E5C808EF7C1986A0CB0955E16DA131631693E44A9D0127ACF3A17F8D29F6615">
		<old>The VSM may deactivate even if you do not press the <term>ESC OFF</term> button to cancel VSM operation. This indicates that a malfunction has been detected somewhere in the MDPS system or VSM. If the ESC indicator light or MDPS warning light remains on, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The VSM may deactivate even if you do not press the <term>ESC OFF</term> button to cancel VSM operation. This indicates that a malfunction has been detected somewhere in the MDPS system or VSM. If the ESC indicator light or MDPS warning light remains on, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="A7EC7C2C3D0D94BF9AE27C17C1946CF1743C14D5687B526EF0D1243183423A59" status="multi">
		<old>If the DBC indicator light turns yellow, the system may have overheated or malfunctioned. If the warning light appears even when the DBC has cooled off, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the DBC indicator light turns yellow, the system may have overheated or malfunctioned. If the warning light appears even when the DBC has cooled off, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="C378C0E3932813855C00BB23F6B6107A3AC85AFBE54E0FA7F50C608747A04514">
		<old>If the ESC or MDPS warning light stays illuminated or blinks, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the ESC or MDPS warning light stays illuminated or blinks, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="141F1B44B5B5D147FD3C95324B8269986BC1CCDA29DE5347D0B8787B5E69E14F">
		<old>If the ISG system continuously does not work correctly, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the ISG system continuously does not work correctly, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="2A1CD09A08E3A7C0E03B87A4B97B2D9EF0BDEC7ADCE65D2A36046384700EC3C8">
		<old>If the AWD warning light (<image/>) remains illuminated on the instrument cluster, your vehicle may have an AWD system malfunction. When the AWD warning light (<image/>) appears, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the AWD warning light (<image/>) remains illuminated on the instrument cluster, your vehicle may have an AWD system malfunction. When the AWD warning light (<image/>) appears, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="293C1D409028911C2603877BB8B60BFD3D5B1DD04B66DD9CA0047A6B46465339">
		<old>Start the vehicle after addressing any issue and waiting 10 minutes. If the message remains up, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Start the vehicle after addressing any issue and waiting 10 minutes. If the message remains up, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="AE06D5C32E358A7E5D7009E2E8721D958A0E98BF6E8DFF4EAA1DDA53515B8FB0">
		<old>Keeping a vehicle in good operating condition is important to both fuel economy and safety. Therefore, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Keeping a vehicle in good operating condition is important to both fuel economy and safety. Therefore, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="490CD35CF870A3F23ADC8568C3476FD83C5FA58978A2DB2CA165E7198E63CED9">
		<old>Winter puts additional burdens on the 12V battery system. Visually inspect the 12V battery and cables as described in the Maintenance section. Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer to inspect your battery to check the level of charge.</old>
		<new>Winter puts additional burdens on the 12V battery system. Visually inspect the 12V battery and cables as described in the Maintenance section. Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="EC10D2DD8022099E04ED5CB5DA332834C8C9A5559CBBFB77904F104404E58C1D">
		<old>In some climates, it is recommended that you use a lower viscosity “winter weight” oil during cold weather. See <xref/>. If you aren’t sure what oil weight you should use, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>In some climates, it is recommended that you use a lower viscosity “winter weight” oil during cold weather. See <xref/>. If you aren’t sure what oil weight you should use, consult a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="C8F3C65787CCC12A4646ADD4662BB06E4EA1E0718930CDE7043295104EBCF384">
		<old>Since laws vary, the requirements for towing trailers, cars, or other types of vehicles or apparatus may differ. Ask an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Since laws vary, the requirements for towing trailers, cars, or other types of vehicles or apparatus may differ. Consult a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B1BD0083250C4C32869249784C8691A6828FEB353DE86A86170AB33BF178980F">
		<old>Have an authorized Kia dealer assist with installing the wiring harness.</old>
		<new>Have the wiring harness installed by a professional workshop.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="92ABEEF10C4A8A7E1A9B73BDA7D8EB66F705B60434BD5578D2A8727AAE91CF27">
		<old>Visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E050689ABFC6EC675CC1AB04A8DDD92927867062C9612370E97B9FF7EC57D19C">
		<old>When towing a trailer, consult an authorized Kia dealer on additional requirements, such as a towing kit.</old>
		<new>When towing a trailer, consult a professional workshop on additional requirements, such as a towing kit. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="99AE3910D0CEDB919D46D6D0EBE8C630AFAA0CEB6DE631466126EB725928DB8C" status="multi">
		<old>If the detection sensors have been replaced or repaired, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the detection sensors have been replaced or repaired, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="6A7EDEB380C88A01A1A602C819C1C9C672224B70023EA86A1DF0708EF2DB9E3A">
		<old>If the vehicle experiences an impact to or around the radar, Forward Collision-avoidance Assist may not operate properly, even if the instrument cluster does not display a warning message. Visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the vehicle experiences an impact to or around the radar, Forward Collision-avoidance Assist may not operate properly, even if the instrument cluster does not display a warning message. Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="DA0A877BFE64DF051983F6A7F4E05C4F779D4C102FB9268C0BD221B28D38E119">
		<old>You can monitor Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist setting status on the Settings menu of the infotainment system screen. If the Forward Safety warning light (<image/>) or Emergency steering warning light (<image/>) remains <term>ON</term> when Forward safety or Forward/Side safety is selected, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>You can monitor Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist setting status on the Settings menu of the infotainment system screen. If the Forward Safety warning light (<image/>) or Emergency steering warning light (<image/>) remains <term>ON</term> when Forward safety or Forward/Side safety is selected, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="BCD2F30B21B7E34F9E31405CD02C94A6DB818E126D9FD6C76D9348F0ABB27EAD">
		<old>When Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>), the Forward Safety warning light (<image/>), and the Emergency Steering warning light (<image/>) appear on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message that lasts for several seconds. Visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>), the Forward Safety warning light (<image/>), and the Emergency Steering warning light (<image/>) appear on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message that lasts for several seconds. Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="BD61819864F51091D66C70AF20C1AF0D2504C307EB4D18CDD5CC42F15C0802AE">
		<old>If Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Forward Collision-Avoidance Assist still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="6B8FAFE3B9492399818DD5BECC7B6C6BB7A5009C404C2E319163956E33B7E57C">
		<old>If a warning message appears, have the Lane Keeping Assist function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If a warning message appears, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="09548A7EABD221A02042CBF1313884539E88FA77028B55A6FD78F55AAA86C694">
		<old>If Lane Keeping Assist still does not operate properly after you clean foreign materials (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or remove obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Lane Keeping Assist still does not operate properly after you clean foreign materials (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or remove obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="A23F038C11ADDF02E18B31E5B123C1EA73C6C825D826BBBC47BDEEBE4062356C">
		<old>If the warning message and Master warning light appear on the instrument cluster, have the Lane Following Assist inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the warning message and Master warning light appear on the instrument cluster, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="FFF4364E22697F19B24E6606C558261A19A760EC27A862D63E61238C560AABF2">
		<old>If the detection sensor or the area near the sensor has been damaged or impacted in any way, Blind-Spot Collision-avoidance Assist may not operate properly, even if a warning message does not appear on the instrument cluster. Have the function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the detection sensor or the area near the sensor has been damaged or impacted in any way, Blind-Spot Collision-avoidance Assist may not operate properly, even if a warning message does not appear on the instrument cluster. Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="45DBDFE20B5651D192CBC568358672A99573CFE78C0ADF3F420EF4832F4D0906">
		<old>When Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message, which lasts for several seconds. You can check the warning-related functions in the Service Messages of the Utility Information View on the cluster display. If this occurs, have Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message, which lasts for several seconds. You can check the warning-related functions in the Service Messages of the Utility Information View on the cluster display. If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="649F7E30ABBA958F68B38FB48321F9349D474F822CD94AC4209E188C6FD1B660">
		<old>When the outside rearview mirror warning light is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message, which lasts for several seconds. If this occurs, have Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When the outside rearview mirror warning light is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message, which lasts for several seconds. If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D3B51584F0A03E9AF33A35FA07D5C3636022B41E014B98E1CE0884AC50CDA2DC">
		<old>If Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Blind-Spot Collision-Avoidance Assist still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B5225CBBED683278A8B57223F6D319ECADEA09885671D6979D186E23F0828EE5">
		<old>When Safe Exit Assist is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message that lasts for several seconds. If it does not work properly, have Safe Exit Assist inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Safe Exit Assist is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message that lasts for several seconds. If it does not work properly, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="02A90A96E421AE03B9A9E4D7987914F93423CCEEE3BD70D45930F0060C40776C">
		<old>Have Safe Exit Assist inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D0833D05686B5F89388895C6989DB6D4F04B90A4573FC4E0FAEBBDBABC1FD170">
		<old>If Safe Exit Assist still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Safe Exit Assist still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="32F3A111BBEAF3746BF1CBE450ED9128798EF2812CD38B9726071581C3F7A371">
		<old>When Blind-Spot View Monitor does not work properly, the instrument cluster display flickers, or the camera image does not display normally, have Blind-Spot View Monitor inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Blind-Spot View Monitor does not work properly, the instrument cluster display flickers, or the camera image does not display normally, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="7D2736FF728C77407876F940A2EDDF351793FD44C5FA26D9C0ECA7C1D8E1943A">
		<old>If this occurs, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="0815D4F48AFD6D821DC0BEC9E81C83AE8B5F93483154EA254C1FACF35FC5DF42">
		<old>If Intelligent Speed Limit Assist still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Intelligent Speed Limit Assist still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1A195D22DF0B64FE48145F029A7D98DD11CD4914961F9F1AD78489BC90EF3857">
		<old>If this occurs, have Driver Attention Warning inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B4F996776B02E338FCE8E19A8471F3CA3E8AAC245D0A6837F25E0B7C7C4F3CAA">
		<old>If Driver Attention Warning still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Driver Attention Warning still does not operate properly after you remove foreign material (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="7E2D7162D6FA52D31CE6E9610C98DD2E9378FAE24C00B66E4BCF14B5EA4EB8B0">
		<old>If this occurs, have the function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer as soon as possible.</old>
		<new>If this occurs, have the function inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="14F58BF39D067B6903639A04FD707614DFEF3F74926BDD6CDC215AE46F58E98B">
		<old>If the object is removed or the camera is able to detect the driver’s face, the function will operate normally. If Forward Attention Warning does not operate properly after the object is removed, have the function checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the object is removed or the camera is able to detect the driver’s face, the function will operate normally. If Forward Attention Warning does not operate properly after the object is removed, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="49A9608C49713F9242F40B16038D779A97CA2FD3C5F1D23A62845B125445A25C">
		<old>When Smart Cruise Control is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message that lasts for several seconds. Have Smart Cruise Control inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Smart Cruise Control is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message that lasts for several seconds. Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="513FF0BE263A856C2AE4D0AB1FFC48BA4E3F074ECE144D4DA28C281AB5E0C7E9">
		<old>When <uicontrol>Emergency Stop</uicontrol> is not working properly, the warning message and Master warning light (<image/>) will appear on the cluster. If this occurs, have the function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When <uicontrol>Emergency Stop</uicontrol> is not working properly, the warning message and Master warning light (<image/>) will appear on the cluster. If this occurs, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="BCA04518E5D575DF4CE65EC43C8356E1BC0A723AFAF21AF86551EE3FF6D51C2C">
		<old>If there is a problem with the Highway Lane Change Assist function, you cannot change the settings and should have the function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If there is a problem with the Highway Lane Change Assist function, you cannot change the settings and should have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="9AF2112379CF2067591ABA265D27A1F37BB4D60374897D939E6AAD304300F33A">
		<old>When Highway Driving Assist is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message that lasts for several seconds. Have Highway Driving Assist inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Highway Driving Assist is not working properly, the Master warning light (<image/>) appears on the instrument cluster, along with a warning message that lasts for several seconds. Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3D7DA6BCA887FB0789BE32BA16B8CA65A1706A592332369815D9A3E1E88575F7">
		<old>Visit an authorized Kia dealer if the Rear View Monitor does not work properly, the screen flickers, or the camera image does not display properly.</old>
		<new>If the Rear View Monitor does not work properly, the screen flickers, or the camera image does not display properly, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="937E12476C8BE855F7850C086FA38C636A498FAD6D09BCE2C948B819999DF7B6">
		<old>Have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer if the Surround View Monitor does not work properly, the screen flickers, or the camera image does not display properly.</old>
		<new>If the Surround View Monitor does not work properly, the screen flickers, or the camera image does not display properly, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="61E2DC80598AF4F8B2D3A0DA7861E54A89ED00342DE53085016F161AB69E5F02" status="multi">
		<old>Have the function inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="75B75D01632E0532D8FD285E4BA9E5AB1939C2313B82B95EEEC4771E04F61E85">
		<old>If Rear Cross-Traffic Collision-Avoidance Assist still does not operate properly after you remove foreign materials (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Rear Cross-Traffic Collision-Avoidance Assist still does not operate properly after you remove foreign materials (such as snow or rain) from the sensor or obstructions (such as a trailer or carrier) from the rear bumper, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="72997F4E551027D9B4C1891D9C6DC0BB6A7224EA11E2289BF06BB4A72CFBC742">
		<old>You can check the contents of the warning in the service message of the utility information view of the instrument cluster. If the function still does not work properly, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>You can check the contents of the warning in the service message of the utility information view of the instrument cluster. If the function still does not work properly, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="9B3132C2006D7969FA63ADF452F883090E21CFA1AA22A1071B4C7670ACB5E5C9">
		<old>The ultrasonic sensors detect objects around your vehicle. Parking Distance Warning may be temporarily limited or may not operate if snow, rain, foreign substances, and so on cover the sensor. You can check the detection sensor blind warning target (ultrasonic sensor) in the service message of the utility information view in the instrument cluster. Parking Distance Warning works normally if you remove the contamination from the recognition sensor. Always keep it clean. If the function still does not work properly even after you remove the contamination, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The ultrasonic sensors detect objects around your vehicle. Parking Distance Warning may be temporarily limited or may not operate if snow, rain, foreign substances, and so on cover the sensor. You can check the detection sensor blind warning target (ultrasonic sensor) in the service message of the utility information view in the instrument cluster. Parking Distance Warning works normally if you remove the contamination from the recognition sensor. Always keep it clean. If the function still does not work properly even after you remove the contamination, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B331129775B03D1146E6940AE54442E1FC9B2E87D39115DBC9D7750DACC1CC5A">
		<old>If Parking Distance Warning does not operate properly, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If Parking Distance Warning does not operate properly, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="47372F76E3E69AFBE526238577329B75EC9C49E50BFD72DA895D2EFDCE86C37F">
		<old>Avoid impacts to the sensors. If a sensor is displaced by impact, Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist may not function properly. If a sensor is damaged due to impact, have it inspected at an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Avoid impacts to the sensors. If a sensor is displaced by impact, Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist may not function properly. If a sensor is damaged due to impact, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="2DC6842229BBF6FE579B5A5C55EA8D6EF0935140F3BCB248133BB87C0886C81F">
		<old>If there is a problem with Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist or related functions and parts, a warning message displays on the instrument cluster. If the function still does not work properly, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If there is a problem with Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist or related functions and parts, a warning message displays on the instrument cluster. If the function still does not work properly, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1B7E60EBBEB77F99FD77BA9E07C3DFF2EBEBC11BCF0333136E57B15BDBC0C09E">
		<old>The wide-rear view camera and rear ultrasonic sensors detect objects around your vehicle. Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist may be temporarily limited or may not operate if snow, rain, foreign substances, and so on obscure the sensor. You can check the detection sensor blind warning target (wide-rear view camera and rear ultrasonic sensor) in the service message of the utility information view in the instrument cluster. Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist works normally if you remove the contamination from the recognition sensor. Always keep it clean. If the function still does not work properly even after you remove the contamination, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The wide-rear view camera and rear ultrasonic sensors detect objects around your vehicle. Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist may be temporarily limited or may not operate if snow, rain, foreign substances, and so on obscure the sensor. You can check the detection sensor blind warning target (wide-rear view camera and rear ultrasonic sensor) in the service message of the utility information view in the instrument cluster. Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist works normally if you remove the contamination from the recognition sensor. Always keep it clean. If the function still does not work properly even after you remove the contamination, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="4335936B2FCD55E6643FF867FC9F1CF41002B10AA54521524A98EE66378C2DAF">
		<old>Do not apply unnecessary force to the Wide Rear View camera or ultrasonic sensors. Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist may not operate properly if you forcibly move the Wide Rear View camera or ultrasonic sensors out of proper alignment. If Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist does not operate properly, visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Do not apply unnecessary force to the Wide Rear View camera or ultrasonic sensors. Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist may not operate properly if you forcibly move the Wide Rear View camera or ultrasonic sensors out of proper alignment. If Parking Collision-Avoidance Assist does not operate properly, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="32906B999E92ED9AB870D0DC6C594B8E2C9BAC7A7DEAA3D1E00DCEC9B8AD7319">
		<old>When Remote Smart Parking Assist is not working properly, the <uicontrol>Check Parking Assist</uicontrol> warning message will appear on the infotainment system screen. If the message appears, stop using the function, and have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>When Remote Smart Parking Assist is not working properly, the <uicontrol>Check Parking Assist</uicontrol> warning message will appear on the infotainment system screen. If the message appears, stop using the function, and have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="5FB9C21C86B7843140FE4EB23A3FF157C67FECB850EBA8F1641110B3104E66ED">
		<old>Remote Smart Parking Assist may not operate normally if the vehicle needs wheel alignment adjustment such as when the vehicle tilts to one side. Have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Remote Smart Parking Assist may not operate normally if the vehicle needs wheel alignment adjustment such as when the vehicle tilts to one side. Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="48B8770B39B84659FD87CF5469EDA0F02FF56033D3E6268D5B661F519D2674AE">
		<old>Be careful not to subject the detection sensors to impact. If the sensors become misaligned due to impact, the Remote Smart Parking Assist may not operate properly. If a sensor is damaged by impact, have it inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Be careful not to subject the detection sensors to impact. If the sensors become misaligned due to impact, the Remote Smart Parking Assist may not operate properly. If a sensor is damaged by impact, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="695A15E610B2AAD55D863163E89EB06B024279E9AA052C570BA4494AD1A9E411">
		<old>If it is not obvious why your battery was discharged, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If it is not obvious why your battery was discharged, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="6B62BEAABA0F239EB3C5C8106706F47921A945EB4B82874DE59217EDCEF7D452">
		<old>Proceed with caution, keeping alert for further signs of the engine overheating. If overheating recurs, have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer for assistance.</old>
		<new>Proceed with caution, keeping alert for further signs of the engine overheating. If overheating recurs, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="03F1D3917ABC66B343EC154F16402569E3553E96984AD3B4E0D89F08F8E1AC62">
		<old>Serious loss of coolant indicates that there is a leak in the cooling system. This should be checked as soon as possible. Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Serious loss of coolant indicates that there is a leak in the cooling system. This should be checked as soon as possible. Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3817229D6DBED9DCD2891EA094804705918D7F215672975324DEF19A22C705EA">
		<old>Try to restart your vehicle. If your vehicle does not restart, contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Try to restart your vehicle. If your vehicle does not restart, contact a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="98028D9DA724FAF0B6BE96E689A585C6A6CAF5510A354300E96517B644AAD713">
		<old>Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer under any of the following circumstances:</old>
		<new>Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner under any of the following circumstances:</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="33F94023DD360EF23E5882A78DAC68DCBA5E1277C96D60D50C6B1F8FA52E1562">
		<old>Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer as soon as possible to determine the cause of the problem:</old>
		<new>To determine the cause of the problem, have the system inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="306E610CDE293CF4E2C4754631A7FA650141E1D3117404604012F33FBA885470">
		<old>If you have a flat tire, the low tire pressure indicator light appears. Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer as soon as possible, or replace the flat tire with the spare tire.</old>
		<new>If you have a flat tire, the low tire pressure indicator light appears. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="98508BAC9E23A050DEE5BA061C9D6FEC054AA5860809616F69B80CEC43090106">
		<old>Each wheel is equipped with a tire pressure sensor mounted inside the tire behind the valve stem. You must use TPMS-specific wheels. Always have your tires serviced by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Each wheel is equipped with a tire pressure sensor mounted inside the tire behind the valve stem. You must use TPMS-specific wheels. Have your tires serviced by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3B9FDD3F1C2AD68B22177275E9B8C30461DD48356CEA4FC0939BD47E8AACDE0D">
		<old>If the indicator light does not turn <term>OFF</term> after a few minutes of driving, visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the indicator light does not turn <term>OFF</term> after a few minutes of driving, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1F10B4050B32B5DA8CEB8881B466D455B73DB374E3F36D7F4798640F97D422AE">
		<old>If you replace an original tire with the spare tire, the TPMS sensor on the replaced spare wheel should be activated, and the TPMS sensor on the original wheel should be deactivated. If the TPMS sensor on the original wheel located in the spare tire carrier is still active, the TPMS may not operate properly. Have the tire with the TPMS serviced or replaced by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If you replace an original tire with the spare tire, the TPMS sensor on the replaced spare wheel should be activated, and the TPMS sensor on the original wheel should be deactivated. If the TPMS sensor on the original wheel located in the spare tire carrier is still active, the TPMS may not operate properly. Have the tire with the TPMS serviced or replaced by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="F1CFD4C118BF73126E4C66D278ECFC683619E9373974B244CEF53B1ED3E08493">
		<old>Position the wrench as shown in the illustration above and tighten the wheel nuts. Make sure the socket is seated completely over the nut. Do not stand on the wrench handle or use an extension pipe over the wrench handle. Go around the wheel, tightening every nut. Double check each nut to be sure it is tight on the wheel. After you change a wheel, have your vehicle consulted by an authorized Kia dealer to tighten the wheel nuts to their proper torque as soon as possible.</old>
		<new>Position the wrench as shown in the illustration above and tighten the wheel nuts. Make sure the socket is seated completely over the nut. Do not stand on the wrench handle or use an extension pipe over the wrench handle. Go around the wheel, tightening every nut. Double check each nut to be sure it is tight on the wheel. After you change a wheel, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop to tighten the wheel nuts to their proper torque as soon as possible. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="52AA960410AAB8FE98B3671F09C2027ABC0F540762E112695B4258ED4941F050">
		<old>Note that most lug nuts do not have metric threads. Be extremely careful and check the thread style before you install aftermarket lug nuts or wheels. If in doubt, have your vehicle consulted by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Note that most lug nuts do not have metric threads. Be extremely careful and check the thread style before you install aftermarket lug nuts or wheels. If in doubt, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D31FE7B2D332C32D4585E22AD520FDC392F39273FBF1B96822DFDF89AF687F20">
		<old>If the Electronic Parking Brake (<term>EPB</term>) does not release normally, take your vehicle to an authorized Kia dealer by loading the vehicle on a flatbed tow truck and have the system checked.</old>
		<new>If the Electronic Parking Brake (<term>EPB</term>) does not release normally, load your vehicle onto a flatbed tow truck and have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="CCF48A1E1FA0FBE207767943EA77E4F55D4324CC9699E99D71E0DD58E0E583F3">
		<old>If the disabled vehicle is unable to be moved, do not forcibly continue the towing. We recommend that you contact an authorized Kia dealer or a commercial tow truck service for assistance.</old>
		<new>If the disabled vehicle is unable to be moved, do not forcibly continue the towing. Contact a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer, service partner or a commercial tow truck service for assistance.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="87773B96C63DC43E8D60EDBD2876E1D32E01F81662D85DF28AE0C5658F4CB581">
		<old>If you have any doubts concerning the inspection or maintenance of your vehicle, have an authorized Kia dealer perform this work.</old>
		<new>If you have any doubts concerning the inspection or maintenance of your vehicle, have an authorized Kia dealer or service partner perform this work.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="378618037599191D64596A0F5350F4D3937339832A0415883CDD96654F18B863">
		<old>Improper owner maintenance during the warranty period may affect warranty coverage. For details, read the separate Warranty and Consumer Information manual provided with the vehicle. If you’re unsure about any servicing or maintenance procedure, have it done by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Improper owner maintenance during the warranty period may affect warranty coverage. For details, read the separate Warranty and Consumer Information manual provided with the vehicle. If you’re unsure about any servicing or maintenance procedure, have your vehicle serviced by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E90A0D88A830C2AAA8F2923B002D38C6869A3EEC8F98D7789E8DA68843D1A300">
		<old>Check to make sure that the front of the radiator and condenser are clean and not blocked with leaves, dirt, insects, and so on. If any of these parts are extremely dirty, or if you are not sure of their condition, take your vehicle to an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Check to make sure that the front of the radiator and condenser are clean and not blocked with leaves, dirt, insects, and so on. If any of these parts are extremely dirty, or if you are not sure of their condition, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B22622C10E010CB91ED72FFD7CF6CCCCC14FA8587205D3FC6F939820BEEEBF11">
		<old>If you notice any slipping or changes in the operation of your transmission, take your vehicle to an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If you notice any slipping or changes in the operation of your transmission, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="8E386DFA128FFBE17E6D84D3F03973B4485E33826025DD42185506303A4AED83">
		<old>If engine oil deteriorates more quickly depending on the severity of your driving, the remaining oil life alert appears on the instrument cluster before the normal engine oil replacement interval. Have the engine oil and filter changed by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If engine oil deteriorates more quickly depending on the severity of your driving, the remaining oil life alert appears on the instrument cluster before the normal engine oil replacement interval. Have the engine oil and filter changed by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E8DAAF600C391A73AFCEBFDF3420511860E5E49E081D6358B4935348ABAC8518">
		<old>If there is no alert until the maximum maintenance interval, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If there is no alert until the maximum maintenance interval, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="ABE89DA4D34E24C373BE76DB2AA190398159D33A6F0782EAB518804BC9BA140C">
		<old>If there are safety risks, such as fuel flow restriction, surging, loss of power, or hard starting problems, replace the fuel filter immediately regardless of the maintenance schedule. Consult an authorized Kia dealer for details.</old>
		<new>If there are safety risks, such as fuel flow restriction, surging, loss of power, or hard starting problems, replace the fuel filter immediately regardless of the maintenance schedule. Consult a professional workshop for details. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="295BFEBD9EB304325E4ECB887ED66EBD01B3B1CC4BE2E2C822FF682238B5E27C">
		<old>If there are safety risks, such as fuel flow restriction, surging, loss of power, hard starting problems, and so on, replace the fuel filter immediately regardless of the maintenance schedule. Consult an authorized Kia dealer for details.</old>
		<new>If there are safety risks, such as fuel flow restriction, surging, loss of power, or hard starting problems, replace the fuel filter immediately regardless of the maintenance schedule. Consult a professional workshop for details. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D003CC5A2E204B12A1DCFED21045588B29A7851C4AEC99F029B61C4A65913524">
		<old>Check the fuel lines, fuel hoses, and connections for leakage and damage. Have the fuel lines, fuel hoses, and connections replaced by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Check the fuel lines, fuel hoses, and connections for leakage and damage. Have the fuel lines, fuel hoses, and connections replaced by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3F1013D9F37A87D28732C8EC640B931AF6E0CC3A6B23BFC17056A4BA8DCD0DCC">
		<old>Have the Genuine Kia air cleaner filter replaced by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Have the Genuine Kia air cleaner filter replaced by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="423FCD6148962C02FA42142EA12ED1752F379D43BE500CFBEE8C03F013D1909A">
		<old>Do not check the automatic transmission fluid under normal usage conditions. Have the automatic transmission fluid changed by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Do not check the automatic transmission fluid under normal usage conditions. Have the automatic transmission fluid changed by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E4E82F3D8DAC57CE978EA2A1B5CB629A5AD113E48CC3D369618B34FF4F4C4F2E">
		<old>The lubrication, rust prevention, cooling, and cleaning effect of the engine oil gradually degrades during its use. Have the engine oil and filter changed by an authorized Kia dealer according to the Engine Oil Life Management System instructions or the maintenance schedule.</old>
		<new>The lubrication, rust prevention, cooling, and cleaning effect of the engine oil gradually degrades during its use. Have the engine oil and filter changed by a professional workshop according to the Engine Oil Life Management System instructions or the maintenance schedule. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="41663E6E36882557A2BD13F456BD1EC1EDB1E6F54961ACFB1301933516BBCEDD">
		<old>If your vehicle requires frequent coolant refills, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If your vehicle requires frequent coolant refills, have the system inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="6F50F80320D8E1774AA61629EF2EF2A7CA0EA3BD24318D410EB8AFC98F94A1F0">
		<old>Have the coolant replaced by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Have the coolant replaced by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="0B2EC6190CD70674B76A947AA4E610628A355C865A76290CCFB78896E9F2E30B">
		<old>If the fluid level is excessively low, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the fluid level is excessively low, have the system inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B82D9E11FA9A8D943B2AE8F13914D8D72FF329F81F7947A198C9CBF0FCF33385">
		<old>If the brake system requires you to add fluid frequently, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the brake system requires you to add fluid frequently, have the system inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="6013DEB8361A1EE546EF63522FBEA9876F765CA67615B78C5B73D7C8C58F82FD">
		<old>To prevent damage to the wiper arm or other components, have the wiper blade replaced by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>To prevent damage to the wiper arm or other components, have the wiper blade replaced by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="39F55BDEEDAF310F79555773C00CD5D14BC109D7353EC311DC93409F4067BCB5">
		<old>Your vehicle is equipped with a maintenance-free 12V battery. If your vehicle’s 12V battery is marked with  <b>LOWER</b> and  <b>UPPER</b> on the side, you can check the electrolyte level. The electrolyte level should be between the  <b>LOWER</b> and  <b>UPPER</b> marks. If the electrolyte level is low, add distilled (demineralized) water. (Never add sulfuric acid or other electrolytes.) When refilling, be careful not to splash the 12V battery and adjacent components. Do not overfill the 12V battery cells, as this can cause corrosion on other parts. Make sure to tighten the cell caps. Contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Your vehicle is equipped with a maintenance-free 12V battery. If your vehicle’s 12V battery is marked with  <b>LOWER</b> and  <b>UPPER</b> on the side, you can check the electrolyte level. The electrolyte level should be between the  <b>LOWER</b> and  <b>UPPER</b> marks. If the electrolyte level is low, add distilled (demineralized) water. (Never add sulfuric acid or other electrolytes.) When refilling, be careful not to splash the 12V battery and adjacent components. Do not overfill the 12V battery cells, as this can cause corrosion on other parts. Make sure to tighten the cell caps. Contact a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="3BDA03C6DD753AFEA0601341E911DCC3E8BD4AFBD1E77705C313F801CEA95C26">
		<old>Absorbent Glass Matt (AGM) batteries are maintenance-free. Have your AGM battery serviced by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Absorbent Glass Matt (AGM) batteries are maintenance-free. Have your AGM battery serviced by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="BBF8BC7BD421728DFFCAE70400804930C22B91B81D73B795CBA0789DCD8ECF77">
		<old>If you receive a warning message on the instrument cluster or a malfunction alert text on your phone, have the system inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If you receive a warning message on the instrument cluster or a malfunction alert text on your phone, have the system inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="0BF6797C457BF297E76B6EE51DD1D0D65150453D62C6AFA0104E64CC1C4D2A99">
		<old>If the tire sustains impact, inspect the tire’s condition or contact an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the tire sustains impact, have the tire inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="CE7798C864036549F381040D04440CCAC32C9DEB4A2981F5EE53DB753440593E">
		<old>If a replacement fuse blows, this indicates an electrical problem. Avoid using the respective system and immediately consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If a replacement fuse blows, this indicates an electrical problem. Avoid using the respective system and have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="17A83BAC2DFE6067550531C88427F301C6053E6932C79573B068244FBFBCA810">
		<old>Do not remove fuses, relays, and terminals fastened with bolts or nuts. The fuses, relays, and terminals may be fastened incompletely and could cause a possible fire. If fuses, relays, and terminals fastened with bolts or nuts are blown, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Do not remove fuses, relays, and terminals fastened with bolts or nuts. The fuses, relays, and terminals may be fastened incompletely and could cause a possible fire. If fuses, relays, and terminals fastened with bolts or nuts are blown, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="A59976927D4CC87F78F0DBD4F5126E6D7AFCD277042CCD967939A579320A59CE">
		<old>If the new fuse does not fit tightly, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the new fuse does not fit tightly, consult a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="07E89EF149585C46B3DE852C516A4F3F59DF9B2026FD912D618F739A99DEECAE">
		<old>If the vehicle’s exterior and interior lamps do not work and their fuses are not blown, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the vehicle’s exterior and interior lamps do not work and their fuses are not blown, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="1323C2746686F356FBB0B5855E4C6DC20F9398096988709FD224A0B4596961F9">
		<old>To replace the blown fuse, push in a new fuse of the same rating and make sure it fits tightly in the clips. If the new fuse does not fit tightly, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>To replace the blown fuse, push in a new fuse of the same rating and make sure it fits tightly in the clips. If the new fuse does not fit tightly, consult a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="8A064525C08DAF9FFCE89F54C4ECB4162DCEE8C2133C1FCCBDDC5BE2F9717E98">
		<old>If the multi-fuse is blown, consult an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the multi-fuse is blown, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="89F3BD1B44F814A604D7DF3504AD63D16D94F90FCDDFDCE3CD320AFBF3437451">
		<old>The electronic system may not function correctly, even when the engine room and internal fuse box’s individual fuses are not disconnected. In this case, the main fuse (BFT type), which is inside the positive 12V battery terminal cap, may be disconnected and causing the malfunction. Because the main fuse is designed more intricately than other parts, you should visit an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>The electronic system may not function correctly, even when the engine room and internal fuse box’s individual fuses are not disconnected. In this case, the main fuse (BFT type), which is inside the positive 12V battery terminal cap, may be disconnected and causing the malfunction. Because the main fuse is designed more intricately than other parts, have it serviced by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="57E8471221F6981FFA8B565EC59A29C53A777AB2B722F9854CCEBF6717BFF93E">
		<old>After an accident or headlamp assembly reinstallation, have the headlamp aim adjusted by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>After an accident or headlamp assembly reinstallation, have the headlamp aim adjusted by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="4B64BF58B4B9D720237B8DFB7C59C89714459E825D9136952F94DDD1C4A93A7D">
		<old>However, if the lamp continues to flicker several times or turns off completely, there may be an error in the vehicle’s electronic control device. In this case, have the vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer immediately.</old>
		<new>However, if the lamp continues to flicker several times or turns off completely, there may be an error in the vehicle’s electronic control device. In this case, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="ED19614C878AA4C81DDAF9CC8EF8F21400C9CAD7299B6F30981E290815B85EC6">
		<old>After you wash your vehicle or drive in the rain, you may find moisture inside the lamp lenses. This is normal condensation caused by the temperature difference between the inside and the outside of the lamp. It does not indicate a problem with the lamp’s functions. The moisture inside the lamp disappears if you drive the vehicle with the headlamps on. However, the level at which moisture dissipates may differ depending on the size, location, and condition of the lamp. If the moisture remains inside the lamp, have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>After you wash your vehicle or drive in the rain, you may find moisture inside the lamp lenses. This is normal condensation caused by the temperature difference between the inside and the outside of the lamp. It does not indicate a problem with the lamp’s functions. The moisture inside the lamp disappears if you drive the vehicle with the headlamps on. However, the level at which moisture dissipates may differ depending on the size, location, and condition of the lamp. If the moisture remains inside the lamp, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="97403F3A0B8F53D7F63D75B5D7544C05AB7D1DC3E601E450B04F131265FFE786">
		<old>If you lack the necessary tools, correct light bulbs, or expertise to replace a light bulb, consult an authorized Kia dealer. In many cases, replacing vehicle light bulbs is difficult because you must remove other parts of the vehicle before you can access the bulb. This is especially true if you have to remove the headlamp assembly to access the bulb.</old>
		<new>If you lack the necessary tools, correct light bulbs, or expertise to replace a light bulb, consult a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner. In many cases, replacing vehicle light bulbs is difficult because you must remove other parts of the vehicle before you can access the bulb. This is especially true if you have to remove the headlamp assembly to access the bulb.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="77D11931F4966BC807F4C186363FA614DEB2DA0BC2CC667096874F8B80A09689">
		<old>If the LED lamp is not functioning, please have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. The LED lamp cannot be replaced as an individual component since it is an integrated unit. Instead, the entire LED lamp unit must be replaced.</old>
		<new>If the LED lamp is not functioning, please have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner. The LED lamp cannot be replaced as an individual component since it is an integrated unit. Instead, the entire LED lamp unit must be replaced.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="02C7B42E774FE31D8C58D2E4F188D39B33B245E28A9F57DDBEADD2938790C29B">
		<old>If the high-mounted stop lamp (LED) is not functioning, please have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer. The LED lamp cannot be replaced as a single unit because it is an integrated component. Instead, the entire LED lamp unit must be replaced. It’s essential to have a skilled technician check or repair the high-mounted stop lamp (LED) to prevent any damage to related vehicle parts.</old>
		<new>If the high-mounted stop lamp (LED) is not functioning, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner. The LED lamp cannot be replaced as a single unit because it is an integrated component. Instead, the entire LED lamp unit must be replaced. It’s essential to have a skilled technician check or repair the high-mounted stop lamp (LED) to prevent any damage to related vehicle parts.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="BA5B2223D4FBAE98301F50E2055AEDA9E9A5735BD2D44863DD9A4FD8BF98B462">
		<old>If the front lights are not functioning, please have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the front lights are not functioning, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="453367618416D8B7332F3619C8E5E3125604C2A820E33BFE2FC346D8F3E50BE3">
		<old>If the side repeater lamp is not functioning, please have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the side repeater lamp is not functioning, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="E388BDAD08B24A054A4571275A9C2CCB4EB5E66459D877CFE19D64EBC06DD5D1">
		<old>If the rear lights are not functioning, please have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the rear lights are not functioning, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="D9BF80895A82B9EC012B91F29964A9CD630971B71A2A77DF95DC6D56327C1268">
		<old>If the interior lights are not functioning, please have your vehicle inspected by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the interior lights are not functioning, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="58E3BF82625E9EEFB7CE4E1CF7829A068D25C6D17F9AAB6B078489D19E9ADBDE">
		<old>If the interior wooden trim is damaged, you may get a splinter from the wood surface. Have your vehicle checked by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>If the interior wooden trim is damaged, you may get a splinter from the wood surface. Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="B0F9D9790FC142B95A633B1A9901585C91DA3AF781B430E1D7E6270DC6557E3F">
		<old>Carbon monoxide (CO) can be present with other exhaust fumes. If you smell exhaust fumes inside your vehicle, have it inspected and have the issue repaired immediately. If you suspect exhaust fumes are entering your vehicle, only drive it with all of the windows fully open. Have your vehicle inspected and repaired immediately by an authorized Kia dealer.</old>
		<new>Carbon monoxide (CO) can be present with other exhaust fumes. If you smell exhaust fumes inside your vehicle, have it inspected and have the issue repaired immediately. If you suspect exhaust fumes are entering your vehicle, only drive it with all of the windows fully open. Have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner.</new>
	</pair>
	<pair hash="68232F5BE2519DA50C9CE3AD2565106264156A8036A1761F95B2EB799374171E">
		<old>If the GPF warning light stays on or <uicontrol>Check exhaust system</uicontrol> message appears in spite of the procedure, visit an authorized Kia dealer. Constant driving with the GPF warning light on can damage the GPF system and undermine fuel economy.</old>
		<new>If the GPF warning light stays on or <uicontrol>Check exhaust system</uicontrol> message appears in spite of the procedure, have your vehicle inspected by a professional workshop. Kia recommends visiting an authorized Kia dealer or service partner. Constant driving with the GPF warning light on can damage the GPF system and undermine fuel economy.</new>
	</pair>
</pairs>