<list>
	<forbidden>
		<item>ACEA C2</item>
		<item>API</item>
		<item>API SN PLUS</item>
		<item>Auto Stop</item>
		<item>AUTO STOP indicator</item>
		<item>Automated Manual Transmission</item>
		<item>Automated Transmission</item>
		<item>Automatic transmission (Shift Lever)</item>
		<item>BI-Fuel</item>
		<item>Biodiesel</item>
		<item>diesel</item>
		<item>Diesel Engine</item>
		<item>DPF</item>
		<item>Dual clutch transmission</item>
		<item>Dual clutch transmission (DCT)</item>
		<item>Dual clutch transmission operation</item>
		<item>emission</item>
		<item>emission control system</item>
		<item>engine</item>
		<item>Engine compartment fuse replacement</item>
		<item>Engine coolant</item>
		<item>Engine coolant reservoir</item>
		<item>Engine coolant temperature gauge</item>
		<item>engine hood</item>
		<item>Engine number</item>
		<item>Engine oil</item>
		<item>Engine oil (diesel)</item>
		<item>Engine oil (Gasoline)</item>
		<item>engine oil and filter</item>
		<item>Engine oil dipstick</item>
		<item>Engine oil filler cap</item>
		<item>engine oil level</item>
		<item>Engine oil pressure warning light</item>
		<item>engine oil level"</item>
		<item>ENGINE START/STOP</item>
		<item>ENGINE START/STOP button</item>
		<item>exhaust</item>
		<item>Exhaust system (DPF) warning</item>
		<item>light (Diesel Engine)"</item>
		<item>FAME</item>
		<item>Fuel</item>
		<item>fuel cap</item>
		<item>fuel containers</item>
		<item>fuel economy</item>
		<item>fuel filler neck</item>
		<item>fuel filter</item>
		<item>Fuel filter cartridge (for diesel engine)</item>
		<item>Fuel filter warning light</item>
		<item>"Fuel filter warning light (Diesel </item>
		<item>Engine)"</item>
		<item>fuel nozzle</item>
		<item>fuel tank</item>
		<item>Gasoline</item>
		<item>"Gasoline containing alcohol and</item>
		<item>methanol"</item>
		<item>Gasoline Engine</item>
		<item>Gasoline Engine</item>
		<item>Gasoline Particulate Filter</item>
		<item>Glow indicator light</item>
		<item>GPF</item>
		<item>GPF system</item>
		<item>GPF warning light</item>
		<item>idle</item>
		<item>Idle Stop and Go</item>
		<item>idle stop and go (ISG)</item>
		<item>ignition</item>
		<item>ignition key</item>
		<item>ignition switch</item>
		<item>ILSAC</item>
		<item>Lean NOx Trap</item>
		<item>lower grade</item>
		<item>lower grade engine oil</item>
		<item>Lubricant</item>
		<item>Manual Transmission</item>
		<item>muffler</item>
		<item>Petrol</item>
		<item>Petroleum</item>
		<item>RON</item>
		<item>ROZ</item>
		<item>RPM</item>
		<item>SAE Viscosity Numbers</item>
		<item>SCR</item>
		<item>SCR warning light</item>
		<item>SCR warning light (Diesel Engine)</item>
		<item>Selective Catalytic Reduction</item>
		<item>Smartstream</item>
		<item>synthetic</item>
		<item>Tachometer</item>
		<item>transmission</item>
		<item>Transmission Control</item>
		<item>Transmission shift indicator</item>
		<item>transmission type</item>
		<item>urea</item>
		<item>Urea Level</item>
		<item>urea solution</item>
		<item>urea solution tank</item>
	</forbidden>
	<exception>
		<item>Check virtual engine sound system</item>
		<item>An electric vehicle is driven using a battery and an electric motor. Whilst general vehicles use an internal combustion engine and petrol as fuel, electric vehicles use electrical energy that is charged and stored inside the high voltage battery.</item>
		<item>As a result, electric vehicles are eco-friendly in that they do not require fuel and do not emit exhaust gases.</item>
		<item>It is driven using the electrical energy that is charged &amp; stored inside the high voltage battery. This method prevents air pollution since fuel, like petrol, is not required, negating the emission of exhaust gases.</item>
		<item>A high performance electric motor is used in the vehicle as well. Compared to standard, internal combustion engine vehicles, engine noise and vibrations are much more minimal when driving.</item>
		<item>This message is displayed when there is a problem with the Virtual Engine Sound System (VESS).</item>
		<item>Virtual Engine Sound System (VESS)</item>
		<item>The Virtual Engine Sound System (VESS) generates an engine sound for pedestrians to hear the vehicle because there is no sound while the Electric Vehicle (EV) is operating.</item>
		<item>The vehicle does not generate an engine sound. Be aware of your driving environment and drive safely.</item>
		<item>When the air bags inflate, they make a loud noise and leave smoke and powder in the air inside of the vehicle. This is normal and is a result of the ignition of the air bag inflator. After the air bag has inflated, you may feel substantial discomfort in breathing due to the contact between your chest and both the seat belt and the air bag, as well as from breathing the smoke and powder.</item>
		<item>Being in or near a police station, government office, broadcasting station, military unit, transmission tower, airport, port, etc.</item>
		<item>Light from a vehicle is not detected because of exhaust fume, smoke, fog, snow, etc.</item>
		<item>Be careful not to contact the antenna when loading cargo on the roof rack. Antenna transmission/reception performance may be degraded.</item>
		<item>Active Sound Design is a feature that makes virtual engine sounds when you press the accelerator pedal for driving pleasure. You can adjust the volume.</item>
		<item>The driver’s face is covered partially by a mask, muffler, dress, etc.</item>
		<item>When objects emitting ultrasonic waves, such as a vehicle's horn, motorcycle engine, or large vehicle air brakes are nearby</item>
		<item>A wireless device with a transmission function operates near the rear ultrasonic sensor</item>
		<item>A wireless device with a transmission function operates near the ultrasonic sensor</item>
		<item>The detecting range of the smart key may vary depending on the surroundings that are affected by radio waves such as transmission tower, broadcast station, etc.</item>
		<item>A wireless device with a transmission function operates near the ultrasonic sensors</item>
		<item>Vehicle propulsion storage type (gasoline/diesel/CNG/LPG/electric/hydrogen)</item>
		<item>Operation of the system is impossible in case of absence of mobile transmission and GPS and Galileo signals.</item>
		<item>Operation of the system is impossible in case of absence of mobile transmission and GPS and GLONASS signals.</item>
		<item>Vehicle propulsion storage type (gasoline/diesel/CNG/LPG/electric/hydrogen)</item>
		<item>Operation of the system is impossible in case of absence of mobile transmission and GPS and Galileo signals.</item>
		<item>The electrical ignition system works with high voltage. Never touch these components with the indicator ON or when the EV button is in the ON position.</item>
		<item>Electronic ATM (Automatic Transmission) Shift Dial</item>
		<item>Front/Rear Corner Radar LH/RH, Front/Rear Inverter, ADAS Driving ECU, VESS (Virtual Engine Sound System) Unit, Front Radar, Front View Camera, ADAS Parking ECU, Console Upper Cover Switch</item>
	</exception>
</list>